AND DAVID
CONE, KAEL, TAKE IT AWAY.
KARL: WELCOME TO CITI FIELD
WHERE THE SKIES HAVE CLEARED,
THE RAIN HAS PASSED, AND YOU CAN
SEE AN OUTSTANDING NIGHT OF
BASEBALL.
GOOD WEATHER, GOOD TEAMS.
THE METS STRUGGLING RIGHT NOW
BUT JUSTIN VERLANDER WILL BE ON
THE BUMP AND HE AND ASKED
SCHERZER HAVE NOT BEEN LEADING
THEM WHERE THEY WANT TO.
CAN HE TURN IT AROUND AGAINST A
FORMER TEAMMATE?
AND THE GUY WHO HAS HAD A
PHENOMENAL SEASON?
GERRIT COLE OF THE NEW YORK
YANKEES.
IT IS THE SUBWAY SERIES.
TWO ACES ON THE MOUND AND THEY
HAVE GOTTEN TOGETHER BEFORE.
YES, ON THE SAME TEAM.
THEY ALSO FACED EACH OTHER.
YOU HAVE TO GO BACK TO 2015.
REMEMBER THE PITTSBURGH PIRATES.
VERLANDER HITS STARLING MARTE IN
THAT GAME.
IT ENDED UP GOING 14 INNINGS.
NEITHER GUY FINISHED AS SOMEBODY
INVOLVED IN THE DECISION.
THEY EACH WENT SIX.
FIVE WALKS FOR VERLANDER IN THAT
GAME.
THEY GOT TOGETHER IN HOUSTON IN
18 AND 19 AND THAT IS WHERE
BRENT STROM CONVINCED THEM,
LET‘S DITCH THE TWO SEAMER AND
GO INTO THE FOUR SEAM FASTBALL.
IT LED VERLANDER TO A WORLD
SERIES TITLE AND MADE BOTH OF
THEM A TON OF MONEY AND NOW,
THEY ARE ON THE SAME FIELD,
FACING OFF AGAINST EACH OTHER AS
WE GET SET FOR THE SECOND NIGHT
OF THE SUBWAY SERIES.
THE YANKEES WON LAST NIGHT 7-6,
IN A GAME THAT REALLY FELT
OLD-SCHOOL.
A LOT OF OFFENSE.
NOT A CRISP GAME.
MAYBE TONIGHT WILL BE DIFFERENT.
WELCOME, EVERYBODY.
1-9 IN THEIR LAST 10.
VERLANDER IS THE GUY.
THEY ARE LOOKING TO HIM TO TURN
THIS THING AROUND.
WHAT WILL IT TAKE FOR HIM TO
FIND THAT AGAIN?
JACKIE: -- DAVID: GET CONFIDENCE
IN HIS FASTBALL AGAIN.
IS IT THE SAME?
ARE HIS SKILLS DIMINISHING?
WE NEED TO GIVE HIM A LITTLE
MORE TIME TO ROUND INTO FORM.
HE HAD A BIG INJURY IN THE BACK
OF HIS SHOULDER.
THE COMPARISON ON THAT FOUR-SEAM
FASTBALL, 2022.
THE VELO, THE INCHES OF DROP.
LESS IS MORE WITH THAT NUMBER
COMPARED TO THIS YEAR.
THE INCHES HAVE DROPPED.
THAT IS THE ACTION.
THE RIDING ACTION ON THE FOUR
SEAMER UP IN THE ZONE.
THE O.P.S. TELLS THE STORY AS
WELL, GETTING HIT.
THIS GUY HAS BEEN
OUTSTANDING.
FRANCISCO ALVAREZ.
THEY ARE WAITING FOR VERLANDER
TO TAKE THE MOUND.
VERLANDER DOES NOT HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT AARON JUDGE.
DOES NOT HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
PETE ALONSO.
AS FAR AS THE OFFENSES GO, WHEN
YOU GET THE NIGHT OFF FROM THOSE
TWO, WHO DO YOU HAVE TO FOCUS
ON?
EDUARDO: GIANCARLO STANTON.
THIS IS HIS HOME AWAY FROM HOME.
24 HOME RUNS.
MORE THAN ANY PLAYER TO HAVE
PLAYED IN THIS BALLPARK.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE NEW YORK
METS AND FRANCISCO LINDOR, HE
HAS TO GET IT GOING ESPECIALLY
SWINGING FROM THE LEFT SIDE
WHERE HE STRUGGLED.
WHAT DID YOU SEE? YOU WERE
HERE LAST NIGHT AND CALLED
AGAIN.
WHAT DID YOU SEE FROM THE TWO
TEAMS?
WHAT WAS THE ATMOSPHERE LIKE?
WHAT CAN FOLKS AT HOME WERE
WATCHING ANTICIPATE?
DAVID: IN MAJOR MARKETS, THE
APPETITE IS STILL HERE.
BIG CROWDS, THE REACTION.
WE SEE LET‘S GO YANKEES CHANTS.
THERE WAS AN ACTION-PACKED GAME.
THE METS DESPERATELY NEED JUSTIN
VERLANDER TO BE JUSTIN VERLANDER
AND KIND OF STOP THIS LOSING
SLIDE TODAY ON RIGHT NOW.
KARL: JAKE BAUERS WILL LEAD
THINGS OFF OF THE YANKEES TO
BEGIN THE NIGHT.
THEY WERE EIGHT GAMES BEHIND
TAMPA BAY.
FOUR GAMES BEHIND THE ORIOLES.
LEMAHIEU, KINER-FALEFA, WHO HAS
HIT THE BALL HARD.
HE GOT OFF TO A REALLY GOOD
START.
ANTHONY HALL B IS AT SHORT.
STARTING LINEUP FOR AARON
BOONE‘S TEAM.
THEY DON‘T STRIKEOUT A TON.
THEY DON‘T RUN A TON.
VERLANDER, THE FASTBALL, LAST
NIGHT, MAX SCHERZER HONG A BUNCH
OF SLIDERS.
VERLANDER NEEDS TO STRIKE GUYS
OUT IN THE UPPER PART OF THE
ZONE.
A QUICK INDICATION OF THIS IS
THE FOUL BALLS.
WE WILL SEE A LOT OF FOUL BALLS
HIT BACK.
IF WE SEE THAT, WE KNOW IT IS
STARTING TO WORK.
SWINGS AND MISSES UP IN THE ZONE
BUT EARLY INDICATIONS WILL LET
YOU KNOW EXACTLY THE HEATER.
KARL: EDUARDO ESCOBAR AT THIRD
BASE.
LINDOR AT SHORTSTOP.
TOMMY PHAM IN LEFT FIELD.
BRANDON NIMMO, OFF HIS GLOVE, A
PLAY HE ACKNOWLEDGED HE SHOULD
HAVE MADE.
STARLING MARTE IS IAN WRIGHT.
FRANCISCO ALVAREZ BEHIND THE
PLATE AS WE GET SET FOR THE
SUBWAY SERIES, TAKE TWO.
HERE WE GO.
THAT FIRST PITCH IS THE FASTBALL
THAT IS IN THERE FOR A STRIKE.
MILLER IS CALLING BALLS AND
STRIKES TONIGHT.
HIGH AT 94.
YOU SAY GIVE A LITTLE MORE TIME.
AFTER A 37 MINUTE RAIN DELAY, HE
GOT LOOSE.
WHAT IS THE RIGHT AMOUNT OF TIME
BEFORE YOU AS A PITCHER KNOW
THAT YOU ARE NOW BACK WHERE YOU
WANT TO BE?
HERE IS THE 1-1.
MISSES AWAY.
DAVID: HE WAS PLAYING CATCH-UP
SINCE SPRING TRAINING WHEN HE
HAD THE MAJOR INJURY.
AS FAR AS GETTING OUT TO A GOOD
START, HE HAS ALWAYS BEEN A GUY
WHO HAS EVOLVED OVER HIS CAREER.
KIND OF SAVING A LITTLE BIT IN
THE HIP POCKET.
KARL: THERE IS A GOOD BREAKING
PITCH IN THERE.
A SLIDER.
DAVID: HE MIGHT NEED TO GO A
LITTLE HARDER EARLY IN THESE
GAMES TO GET ESTABLISHED ON THE
FOUR SEAM FASTBALL AND SEND A
MESSAGE THAT HE IS BACK.
KARL: THERE IS THIS FOUL BALL.
DAVID: THAT WAS -- EDUARDO: THAT
WAS OFF THE SLIDER BUT STILL
SHOWED THE ACTION.
BEFORE THE GAME, I SAID 6.5
AROUND THIS AREA.
THAT IS ONE.
WE ARE SIX PITCHES IN.
KARL: TOMMY JOHN SURGERY FOR
VERLANDER A COUPLE YEARS AGO.
THE INCREDIBLE CY YOUNG SEASON.
18-4 LAST YEAR.
ANOTHER ONE FOULED OFF.
95.
EIGHT YEARS OLDER THAN GERRIT
COLE.
HUGE EXPECTATIONS ON THE GUY WHO
HAD A LEAD LAST NIGHT, SHIRTS
AND VERLANDER FROM THE METS,
THEIR FANS, FRONT OFFICE OF THE
OWNER.
2-2.
THREE CONSECUTIVE FOUL BALLS.
DAVID: ROLANDA FEELS HE CAN
PITCH FOR SEVERAL MORE YEARS.
HE WANTS TO GET TO 4000
STRIKEOUTS.
HE IS ALREADY IN COOPERSTOWN.
NO DOUBT ABOUT THAT.
THIS GUY IS NOT SATISFIED.
HE WILL LOOK AT THIS AS A BLIP
ON THE SCREEN IN THESE FIRST
EIGHT OR NINE STARTS OF 2023.
EDUARDO: GIANCARLO STANTON.
YOU HAVE TO LOVE THE FACT THAT
YOU ARE ON DECK AND SEEING ALL
THESE PITCHES ALREADY.
FASTBALL SLIDER AND THEN THE
CURVEBALL.
KARL: THIS ONE IS PUT IN PLAY.
INTO THE CORNER HE GOES.
VERLANDER GIVES IT A LOOK AND
PHAM MAKES THE PLAY IN FOUL
TERRITORY.
IT RESULTS IN AND OUT.
EDUARDO: NOT A LOT OF FOUL
TERRITORY THERE.
YOU GET THE WALL AND YOU HAVE TO
FOCUS ON THE WALL.
TOOK A PEEK AT IT EARLY.
HE HAD TO BRACE HIMSELF.
KARL: THE CITY FEEL DESTROYER,
GIANCARLO STANTON, 24 HOME RUNS
AT THIS BALLPARK.
ROLANDA JUMPS AHEAD FOR THE
FASTBALL AT 94.
DAVID: JUSTIN VERLANDER WITH A
BIG BREATH OF RELIEF THERE.
A LONG FIRST AT-BAT PAINTS THAT
PITCH TO GIANCARLO STANTON.
KARL: 38 CAREER HOME RUNS
AGAINST THE METS, MOST AGAINST
ANY OPPONENT.
THERE ARE THE NUMBERS BACKED UP
BY HARPER AND FREDDIE FREEMAN.
MORE OF A HIGH FLY HOMER INSTEAD
OF ONE OF THOSE MISSILES THAT WE
HAVE SEEN HIM GET.
THIS ONE RIGHT OFF THE SCREEN.
EDUARDO: THIS IS WHERE JUST IN,
FOULED OFF THE 1-2.
HOT PART OF THE ZONE USUALLY
ELEVATES.
A LITTLE BIT MORE NOW.
TRY AND GET THAT OUT OF THE
ZONE.
CLIMBING THE LADDER.
DAVID: WE TEND TO THINK ABOUT
COMMAND AS BEING EAST AND WEST.
INSIDE CORNER, OUTSIDE CORNER.
COMMAND OVER THE TOP LINE.
BIG DEAL FOR JUSTIN VERLANDER.
IN RIGHT ON THE LINE OR JUST
ABOVE IT.
EDUARDO: HOW ABOUT THE
21-YEAR-OLD FRANCISCO ALVAREZ?
THROW THIS ONE IN THE DIRT.
THIS IS WHERE I WANT IT.
I WILL BLOCK IT.
A LOT OF ENERGY BEHIND THE PLATE
THERE.
KARL: 15TH PITCH FOR VERLANDER.
GOOD TAKE FROM STANTON.
THE COUNT GOES FULL.
3-2.
DAVID: THERE HAS TO BE A MESSAGE
TO THE PITCHER WHEN THE BALL IS
FOULED OFF.
MORE SWINGS AND PITCHES FOR
VERLANDER.
STRIKEOUT RAIN IS -- STRIKEOUT
RATE IS DOWN.
KARL: HE WENT TO FIRST BASE.
ROBERTO ORTIZ.
STANTON STRIKES OUT.
DAVID: DOUBLED UP.
GOT STANTON ON THE SECOND ONE.
KARL: HERE COMES JOSH JOHNSON
THE THIRD BASEMAN CAME ON --
JOSH JOHNSON, AND THE THIRD-BASE
MONKEY MAN CAME IN AS A HITTER.
CALLED STRIKE.
DEFENSE, MCNEIL SHADED UP.
THIS NON-SHIFT WORLD.
IT IS 1-1.
FIVE HOMERS, 37 R.B.I.‘S.
FIVE HOMERS COME IN 14 GAMES.
LOLLIPOP CURVEBALL AND 79 MILES
PER HOUR.
HIGH HEAT HERE.
DAVID: HE CAN PITCH BACKWARDS,
YES.
THE SLIDER HAS LOOKED VERY
SHARP.
TOOK ANOTHER SHOT THERE WITH IT.
THE IDEA OF PITCHING BACKWARDS
IS THROWING BREAKING BALLS EARLY
IN THE COUNT AND THEN FINISHING
WITH THAT HIGH FASTBALL.
KARL: THE BREAKING PITCH.
ANOTHER ONE IN THE DIRT.
EDUARDO: INTERESTING, SO FAR.
TWO CURVEBALLS.
THAT LAST ONE IS THE SLIDER
RIGHT THERE.
FOURTH SLIDER IS ONE CURVEBALL.
NOTHING STRAIGHT.
THIS IS THE TIME YOU ELEVATE.
KARL: SEVEN FOUL BALLS THIS
INNING.
ON A FAIRLY COMFORTABLE NIGHT,
VERLANDER IN THIS FIRST INNING
IS WORKING UP A SWEAT, 23RD
PITCH.
DONALDSON STRIKES OUT.
VERLANDER‘S SECOND STRIKEOUT OF
THE INNING.
IT CAME ON A FOUR SEAM FASTBALL
THAT WAS 95.5 MILES PER HOUR.
HE WORKED HARD BUT THE METS DID
NOT
KARL: HERE IS GERRIT COLE.
HE WILL TAKE THE MOUND FOR THE
YANKEES WITH A 2.4 E.R.A.
-- 2.84 E.R.A.
THE LONG BALL HUNTING HIM A
LITTLE BIT.
DAVID: HE CAME BACK
DOWN-TO-EARTH, A REGRESSION TO
THE MEAN.
A CAREER-HIGH LAST YEAR.
HE‘S THE TYPE OF PITCHER THAT
CHALLENGES A LOT OF HITTERS AS
HE GETS A LOT OF THE PLATE AND
HE WILL BE PRONE TO GIVING UP
SOME HOMERS HERE WERE THERE.
THE QUESTION IS WHETHER
THEY ARE SOLO SHOTS ARE NOT.
-- OR NOT.
KARL: ALVAREZ, BEATY, PHAM,
ESCOBAR, VIENTOS WILL SET THE
DEFENSE.
DOES NOT SWING AT THE FIRST ONE.
DONALDSON IS AT THIRD.
DJ LEMAHIEU MOVES TO SECOND
TONIGHT AND RIZZO‘S AT FIRST.
KENNETH LEFT THE INCENTIVE.
BOWERS, LEFT TO RIGHT.
JOSÉ TREVINO BEHIND THE PLATE.
ANOTHER ONE AT 95.
VERLANDER WORKED HARD.
23 PITCHES, 15 STRIKES.
THE FIFTH MOST AGAINST ROLANDA
AND THE MOST IN THE FIRST
INNING.
NIMMO FOULS IT BACK.
27 R.B.I.‘S.
THREE STOLEN BASES FOR THE
LEADOFF HITTER.
HOME RUN LAST NIGHT, IF CAREER
LEADOFF HOMER.
HE FINDS HIMSELF IN A FULL COUNT
SITUATION.
EDUARDO: BOTH LEADOFF HITTERS
ARE DOING EXACTLY WHAT THEY ARE
SUPPOSED TO DO.
LONG AT-BATS.
SO FAR, BRANDON NIMMO HAS BEEN
ABLE TO REPLICATE EXACTLY WHAT
JAKE BAUERS WAS DOING IN THAT
FIRST AT-BAT OF THE GAME.
KARL: THAT IS GOING TO BE A
SOUVENIR, SUBWAY SERIES
SOUVENIR.
7-1 ON THE YEAR.
THIS IS HIS 15TH START OF THE
SEASON.
TWO RUNS OR FEWER IN 11 OF THE
GAMES HE STARTED.
THE YANKEES ARE VERY SUCCESSFUL
WHEN HE STARTS.
11-3 IN THE 14 GAMES.
DAVID: YANKEES BULLPEN IS A
LITTLE THIN TONIGHT AFTER BEING
EXTENDED PRETTY HARD LAST NIGHT
IN RECENT GAMES AS WELL AND THE
METS ARE A PITCHER SHORT BECAUSE
OF THE SUSPENSION.
KARL: SMITH CAUGHT WITH STICKY
SUBSTANCE AND AS A RESULT, 10
GAME SUSPENSION.
NIMMO IS GONE.
98.
A COUPLE UP THE VELOCITY.
THAT IS IN THERE.
DAVID: LIFE AND COMMAND.
GREAT SHOT OF HOW EFFICIENT THAT
BACKSPIN WAS ON THE PITCH.
NOT ONLY THE SPIN AND THE
VELOCITY BUT THE LOCATION RIGHT
AT THE TOP OF THE LINE.
HITTING NIMMO UNDERNEATH THE
PITCH.
KARL: STARLING MARTE, NEXT UP.
ANOTHER ONE AT 96.
AS A HITTER, YOU START TO SEE
95, 95, 96, AND THEN 98 SHOWS
UP.
EDUARDO: THAT IS WHY YOU KNOW
YOU ARE IN TROUBLE, ESPECIALLY
UP IN THE ZONE.
THE VELOCITY AND THE DEPTH.
BETTER THAN EXPECTED.
YOU MENTIONED IT EARLIER.
HE HAS A BIG ZONE AMONGST THE
BIGGEST IN THE LEAD.
KARL: 0-2, MARTE JAMMED ON THAT
ONE.
AFTER THAT 98, SEEMED TO FALL
DEEPLY IN LOVE WITH THE FOUR
SEAM FASTBALL.
STATCAST, POWERED BY GOOGLE
CLOUD.
AS FAR AS EFFECTIVE PICTURES GO,
HIS FOUR SEAMER IS RIGHT THERE
ALONG WITH MORTON‘S CURVEBALL.
THAT IS ALSO ON THE LIST.
DAVID: A THROWBACK IN AN ERA
WHERE PITCHERS ARE THROWING
HARDER THAN EVER BEFORE AND THEY
ARE THROWING LESS FASTBALLS
COLLECTIVELY.
HARD TO FIGURE OUT.
COULD HAVE PITCHED 20 OR 30
YEARS AGO.
KARL: THROWING 97.
YOU HAVE THROWN NINE STRAIGHT
STRIKES.
TRYING TO GO HERE IN THE FIRST.
89 MILE PER HOUR SLIDER AND A
GOOD HALF INNING FROM GERRIT
COLE.
DAVID: A REALLY GOOD LASER --
RAZOR BLADE SLIDER.
FINISHES STRONG.
KARL: ROLANDA STARTED IT AND
ENDED UP GETTING COUPLE OF
PUNCHES AND THEN IT WAS GERRIT
COLE.
ROCK SOLID.
HE PICKS UP TWO STRIKEOUTS IN
THE FIRST.
WE ARE UNDERWAY.
SUBWAY SERIES, SUPER PITCHERS ON
THE MOUND.
KARL: ANTHONY RIZZO WILL LEAD
OFF THE SECOND INNING.
ISIAH KINER-FALEFA HAS HIT THE
BALL A LOT HARDER THIS YEAR AND
WILL BAT THIRD AND VERLANDER
BACK ON THE BUMP AFTER HIS 23
PITCHES IN THE FIRST.
RIZZO WATCHED THAT ONE GO AT 92
MILES PER HOUR.
FOUR FIRST PITCH STRIKES, FIRST
FOUR HE HAS FACED.
0-24 SKID LAST NIGHT.
2-34 SINCE HIS NECK INJURY.
A LOT OF FOLKS MAKE THE
CORRELATION WITH JUDGE.
HE HAS ALSO STRUGGLED.
THEY LOOKED AT HIM AND LEMAHIEU
TO BE THE GUYS TO CARRY THE TEAM
WITHOUT AARON JUDGE.
EDUARDO: YESTERDAY, THEY DID.
THEY TOOK THE FIELD BY ANTHONY
RIZZO.
HOME RUN BY LEMAHIEU.
KARL: SWING VERLANDER BEHIND 3-1
TO RIZZO.
DAVID: IT‘S CLEAR THAT REMAINDER
IS PITCHING OFF OF HIS BREAKING
BALL TONIGHT.
2-1 SLIDER RIGHT THERE.
KARL: RIZZO FRUSTRATED WITH THE
STRIKE CALL.
HE CALLS THE TIME.
EDUARDO: HE WAS 94, 95 AND THE
FIRST INNING.
TWO FASTBALLS.
ANOTHER ONE AT 92.
KARL: NIMMO CALLS OFF MARTE AND
HE IS THERE TO MAKE THE PLAY.
DAVID: A SUBJECT OF
CONVERSATION.
MUCH HAS BEEN INVESTED IN A
PITCHERS.
SURE IS A, 43.
ROLANDA, THE SAME.
THEY ARE WAITING TO GET
PRODUCTION FROM CARRASCO.
JOSÉ QUINTANA HAD A REHAB
ASSIGNMENT AND STARTED
YESTERDAY.
BUCK SHOWALTER INCOME -- AND
COMPANY ARE ENCOURAGED BY THAT
AND HOPING TO GET HIM BACK.
A STARTERS E.R.A. OF OVER 5.00.
EDUARDO: THAT HAS -- DAVID: THAT
HAS GOT TO CHANGE FOR THEM TO
GET BACK IN IT AND PUT TOGETHER
A SUSTAINED STREAK.
KARL: LEMAHIEU WITH SEVEN HOMERS
THIS SEASON AND THAT ONE IS AT
94 MILES PER HOUR.
INTERESTING EVEN THE AGE THAT
WILL BECOME A TOPIC OF
CONVERSATION WITH THE PITCH
CLOCK.
AND YOUR ABILITY TO WITHSTAND
LONG INNINGS, ESPECIALLY AS YOU
GET INTO THE HEAT OF THE SUMMER.
LEMAHIEU BANGS THAT ONE IN THE
GROUND.
DAVID: IN WATCHING RIZZO CALLED
TIME OUT, YOU WONDER, DID HE DO
THE PITCHER A FAVOR?
HITTERS ARE IN THEIR OWN MINDSET
AND WORRIED ABOUT THEIR OWN SORT
OF APPROACH.
THERE‘S STILL ADJUSTMENT GOING
ON WITH PITCHERS AND VETERANS.
GIVE YOURSELF A LITTLE EXTRA
TIME.
THERE SHOULD BE NO MOUND VISITS
LEFT ON THE SCOREBOARD.
FIVE PER GAME.
TAKE A BREAK HERE OR THERE.
KARL: STRIKE ONE.
92 MILES PER HOUR.
TOP OF THE ZONE TO KINER-FALEFA
WHO IS PLAYING CENTER FIELD.
THREE HOMERS, 15 R.B.I.‘S.
THREE HOMERS IN HIS LAST 13
GAMES.
JUST DID NOT BEND LOW ENOUGH.
DAVID: LOOKS LIKE HE‘S SWINGING
HARD.
LOOKS LIKE HE‘S MANY MORE SWEET
SPOTS AND BARRELS.
LETTING IT GO A LITTLE MORE THIS
YEAR.
TRYING TO DRIVE THE BASEBALL.
KARL: YOU CAN SEE IT THROUGH THE
EYES OF THE UMPIRE, BILL MILLER.
DAVID: 10 OF 11 TALKED ABOUT
LAST ARE PLAYING SHORTSTOP.
HE THOUGHT IT WAS MORE IMPORTANT
TO MAKE CONTACT.
TRYING TO HIT FOR A LITTLE MORE
POWER.
KARL: HE CHASED AND VERLANDER,
GOOD INNING.
HE GETS RIZZO AND THE MAYHEW ON
A GROUNDER AND KINER-FALEFA TO
STRIKEOUT.
HE HAS THREE STRIKEOUTS THROUGH
TWO AND HE HAS FACED SIX.
KEVIN: KEVIN CONNORS IN STUDIO.
WE SAW MCCUTCHEN GET HIS 200
CAREER HIT AGAINST THE METS.
TONIGHT, HE TAKES DREW SMYLY
DEEP.
CARLOS SANTANA HAS ADDED A SHOT.
IT IS 3-0.
KARL: THEY ARE RED HOT.
BRYAN REYNOLDS HAD A HIT IN THE
FIRST INNING.
SOMETHING COOKING IN A VARIETY
OF CITIES WHERE THERE HAS NOT
BEEN A LOT ON THE STOVE.
ARLINGTON WITH THE WAY THE
RANGERS ARE PLAYING.
ARIZONA, THE DIAMONDBACKS HAVE
BEEN OUTSTANDING.
UPDATES FROM K.C. ALL NIGHT
LONG.
GIANTS CREEPING AND HANGING,
TOO.
YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT
ABOUT THAT.
EDUARDO: HOW GOOD HAS CORBIN
CARROLL BEEN FOR ARIZONA?
KARL: HE HAS BEEN GREAT.
VERY EXCITING YOUNG PLAYERS IN
THE GAME TODAY.
LINDOR SENDS THAT TO THE SEATS.
EDUARDO: THAT MAN RIGHT THERE
GOT A HAIRCUT CALLED THE EDGAR.
CHECK THAT OUT.
HE HAS THE TWO LINES.
TIED UP TOP.
SOMETHING HAS TO GIVE.
HE‘S HOPING IT WILL HOLD HIM
DOWN.
DAVID: IS EDGAR SOMEBODY WE
SHOULD KNOW?
EDUARDO: NO, IT IS CALLED THE
EDGAR, THE HAIRCUT.
CLASSIC FADE.
KARL: RIZZO, SMOOTH.
IT IS A FOOT RACE.
LINDOR WON IT.
ROBERTO ORTIZ.
HE HAD TO GET ON THAT GIDDYUP
BECAUSE LINDOR SENSED I GOT A
HIT HERE.
EDUARDO: REALLY GOT HIM.
DAVID: GOOD SPEED BY ANTHONY
RIZZO TO GET IT TO HIM THAT SOON
SO HE COULD FIND THE BACK
QUICKER.
MULTITASKING OVER THERE AND YOU
CANNOT GET THE THROW QUICK
ENOUGH.
EDUARDO: HUSTLE DOWN TO GET BACK
ON THE MOUND.
KARL: AS A RESULT, HE SWAPPED
OUT OF BASEBALL.
HE THROWS ONE BY FRANCISCO
ALVAREZ.
DAVID: MARK CANHA PLAYED FIRST
BASE AND HE DID A GOOD JOB OF
GETTING THE BALL AND GETTING RID
OF IT.
RIZZO IS SO COMFORTABLE AND
NONCHALANT IN THE WAY HE MAKES
THOSE PLAYS.
HE ALMOST LULLS YOU TO SLEEP.
KARL: 0-2 TO ALVAREZ.
12 HOMERS.
20 FUN IF -- 25 RUNS BATTED IN.
PICKED UP HIS THIRD STRIKEOUT.
EDUARDO: HE WENT -- THAT WAS ON
AN ELEVATED FASTBALL.
FRANCISCO ALVAREZ.
YOU CANNOT PAINT IT ALL OVER THE
QUADRANT.
AWAY THIS TIME UP.
HARD TO LET THAT ONE GO BY, TOO.
HE WENT THERE.
PUERTO RICO.
KARL: I HEAR WHAT HE SAID.
EDUARDO: I LIKE THAT.
YADIER MOLINA WITH THE
BASKETBALL TEAM.
KARL: HE MENTALLY THINKS NOBODY
IS GETTING THE FASTBALL.
DAVID: HE‘S POURING THE
FOUR-SEAMER IN THERE.
TREMENDOUS CARRY.
KARL: DOWN TO BEATY.
MIKE VERLANDER, EFFECTIVE
STARTING THIS GAME.
CHASING STRIKE ONE.
SIX ASSISTS ON FIRST PITCH
STRIKES, LOOKING FOR STRIKEOUTS.
A COUPLE OF HITS YESTERDAY FOR
BEATY.
SPOILS THAT ONE.
THE COACH OUT THERE WANTS TO
PLAY THE YOUNG GUYS, GET VIENTOS
IN THE LINEUP.
MARISE YOU‘RE DOWN IN THE
MINORS.
DAVID: THERE IS A BIG ADJUSTMENT
PERIOD THAT THESE GUYS HAVE TO
MAKE.
EVERY NIGHT, YOU‘RE GETTING GOOD
PITCHERS.
KARL: JUST GOT GREAT VELOCITY
AND THAT IS A BIG ADJUSTMENT.
DAVID: GREAT POINT BEFORE THE
GAME AS WELL AS.
THE PROSPECTS ARE THERE.
THE GUYS ARE HANGING ON AND
RECYCLED A LITTLE BIT.
NIGHT IN AN NIGHT OUT.
THERE IS BIG DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
MAJOR LEAGUE PITCHING AND
TRIPLE-A PITCHING.
KARL: FIVE STARTERS IN THE
MAJORS IS LIKE, REALLY?
MCKINNEY DID NOT HAVE TO MOVE
MUCH.
SIX UP AND SIX DOWN.
ALRIGHT.
THE CY YOUNG GUYS ARE PITCHING
LIKE THAT TO START.
KARL: HERE WE GO.
THAT GAME IS NEXT.
IT FEELS OLD-SCHOOL, WEDNESDAY
NIGHT DOUBLEHEADER ON ESPN.
TIM ANDERSON GETTING SET.
WHITE SOX DEAL WITH CLAYTON
KERSHAW AND THE DODGERS AT 10:00
EASTERN TIME, ESPN2.
THE GREAT HIM.
GONZALEZ ON THE TELECAST AS WELL
AS.
YOU CAN WATCH BASEBALL LIVE OR
ON-DEMAND, SAVE 50% FOR FATHER‘S
DAY THROUGH JUNE 18.
LACK OUT AND OTHER RESTRICTIONS
APPLY.
THIS ONE TRIP TO RIGHT CENTER.
THAT ONE WILL BOUNCE OVER THE
WALL.
BILLY MCKINNEY WILL HAVE HIMSELF
A LEADOFF DOUBLE TO START THE
INNING.
EDUARDO: FIRST PITCH HE SEES
FROM JUSTIN VERLANDER, FASTBALL
RIGHT DOWN THE MIDDLE.
BARRELS INTO THE GAP.
GIVEN UP BY A JUSTIN VERLANDER
IN THIS GAME.
FIRST BASE RUNNER TO REACH
SECOND VERSUS JUSTIN.
KARL: AND THE FIRST YANKEE TO
SWING AT A FIRST PITCH AGAINST
VERLANDER.
MAYBE A CONVERSATION.
BOY, DON‘T BE AFRAID.
HE HAS NOW HIT SAFELY IN EACH OF
HIS SEVEN GAMES.
JOSÉ TREVINO, NEXT.
MCKINNEY RETREATS QUICKLY.
LINDOR ON ONE PITCH.
TRIVINO IS OUT.
EDUARDO: HE HAS TO MOVE THAT
RUNNER OVER ONE WAY OR ANOTHER.
NEW SCHOOL BASEBALL OR
OLD-SCHOOL BASEBALL, IF YOU ARE
THE BOTTOM OF THE ORDER, YOU TRY
AND CREATE MOMENTUM.
GET THAT FIRST DOUBLE.
YOU ARE GOING TO HAVE A SWING
LIKE THAT.
TOWARDS THE RIGHT SIDE.
GOOD JOB BY GOING WITH THE
SLIDER.
KARL: SHORTSTOP, ANTHONY VOLPE.
IT IS 0-1.
HEADLINES IN NEW YORK.
CONSULTATION WITH HIS MINOR
LEAGUE TEAMMATE, AUSTIN WELLS.
JUST TWEAKING SOMETHING.
LOOKING BACK AT SOME VIDEO FOR
THE MINOR LEAGUES.
EDUARDO: I HEARD THE CHICKEN
PARMESAN WAS GOOD.
KARL: THAT IS INSIDE.
EDUARDO: NOT ONLY DID HE CLOSE
IT, HE ALSO GOT CLOSER TO THE
PLATE.
IT‘S REALLY INTERESTING BECAUSE
THE PICTURES HE STRUGGLED ON
THIS YEAR HAS THE PITCHES IN.
UP AND DOWN.
HE HAS BEEN VERY SUCCESSFUL ON
PITCHES AWAY.
KARL: HOLD TO BE -- HOLTBY HAS
NINE HOME RUNS.
LAYING ON HIS SHOULDER TO START.
A LOT CLOSER TO THE PLATE.
NIMMO GOING OVER, NOW GOING
BACK, MAKES THE PLAY.
HE WAS NOT IN GOOD POSITION TO
THROW THE BALL IN.
HE MAKES AN EASY JAUNT TO THIRD.
EDUARDO: THAT IS WHAT I TALKED
ABOUT WITH THE RUNNER AT SECOND
BASE, AND  NO OUT.
MOST LIKELY AGAINST GERRIT COLE
ON THE OPPOSING SIDE OF IT.
HE FORCED SHOWALTER TO BRING THE
INFIELD IN.
THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN A SAC FLY.
RUNNER AT THIRD AND TWO.
KARL: IT WAS A PAIN FOR A LAND
TIME.
GETS THE INSIDE PITCH AND
DOESN‘T.
NINE PITCH AT-BAT FOR BAUERS TO
LEAD THE GAME OFF.
JUSTIN VERLANDER HAS ALREADY
THROWN 43 PITCHES.
SEVENTH ROUND PICK OF THE PADRES
BACK IN 2013.
DAVID: TALKING TO AARON BOONE
ABOUT JAKE BAUERS.
THEY REALLY LIKE HIS SWING.
THEY THINK THERE IS A PLACE FOR
HIM EVEN WHEN AARON JUDGE COMES
BACK AND HE FACTORED INTO THE
DECISION TO RELEASE AARON HICKS
AS WELL AS.
KARL: 1-2.
THAT‘S A LITTLE HIGH.
ISN‘T IT AMAZING?
DRAFTED IN 13 OF THE PADRES --
UP AND DOWN AND ALL OF A SUDDEN,
HERE YOU ARE WITH AN OPPORTUNITY
FOR THE YANKEES AND HE CAN JUST
TAKE ADVANTAGE.
FEELS LIKE DOING THE SAME THING.
A GROUND FROM VERLANDER AND IT
WAS A LITTLE HARDER AT 96 MILES
PER HOUR.
DAVID: WE MENTIONED IT LAST
WEEKEND IN L.A. ABOUT THE
YANKEES GETTING SO MUCH
LEVERAGE.
THE CALHOUN ALSO IN THAT
CATEGORY AS WELL.
KARL: BIG GO-AHEAD HIT LAST
NIGHT IN THIS ONE.
HE LAYS OFF THAT.
VERLANDER WAS LOOKING FOR A
CALL.
BOWERS, CALHOUN, MCKINNEY.
NO JUDGE AND NO TIMETABLE AT
ALL.
AARON BOONE HAS ZERO INTEL OR
INFORMATION ON THAT.
THIS ONE IS TOWARDS THE SEATS,
GIVING A LOOK AT ESCOBAR.
IT GETS OVER THE FENCE AND THE
WALL.
EDUARDO: A BREAKING PITCH,
ANOTHER CURVEBALL.
HE HAS NOT GONE WITH THE
FASTBALL IN CANS LIKE THIS.
HE HAS NOT TRUSTED THE FASTBALL.
AGAINST THE FASTBALL IN THE
FIRST PITCH.
DAVID: HOLD TO BE -- HOLTBY HIT
A FASTBALL, TOO.
IT‘S HARD TO PLAY THE LOW GAME
WITHOUT THE HIGH GAME.
FASTBALL UP.
SLIDER DOWN.
KARL: ANOTHER GOOD AT-BAT FROM
BOWERS.
HERE IS THE EIGHTH FOUL BALL.
EDUARDO: THIS WILL BE THE 18TH
PITCH THAT BOWERS WILL SEE THIS
INNING.
FOULS OFF PITCHES.
FOUR FOUL BALLS IN THE FIRST
AT-BAT.
FOUR IN THIS ONE.
CRUSHING THE BUDGET.
ON THE WAY TO CRUSHING IT.
KARL: BY THE END OF THE NIGHT,
WE MAY HAVE IT.
DAVID: MY BROADCAST PARTNER
CALLS THAT PITCH THE CVS
PHARMACY.
EDUARDO: [LAUGHTER]
DAVID: DO YOU WANT A RECEIPT?
THAT IS YOUR RECEIPT.
KARL: SKY HIGH.
THIS ONE IN FAIR TERRITORY.
MARTE MAY NOT SEE IT AND THAT‘S
OK BECAUSE IT WAS OUT THERE TO
GET IT.
MARTE DID NOT SEE WHERE THAT
BALL WENT.
COLLEGE WORLD SERIES SUPER
REGIONAL.
GEORGE SPRINGER GOING DEEP WITH
A SOLO HOME RUN.
JOSE BERRIOS AND WHAT HAS BEEN A
NICE BOUNCEBACK YEAR.
BOTTOM OF THE SIXTH.
KARL: TAKE A LOOK AT THE TOP
SEVEN PAYROLLS IN BASEBALL.
THE METS WAY OUT IN FRONT.
THE YANKEES ARE A WILD-CARD.
NOBODY IS IN FIRST PLACE.
THE DODGERS ARE A WILD-CARD
BECAUSE ARIZONA IS PLAYING SO
WELL.
HOW ABOUT THE WAY THE ANGELS ARE
PLAYING?
THEY ARE COMING QUICKLY.
DAVID: INTERESTING YEAR SO FAR
WITH THE HIGH PAYROLL AND THOSE
TEAMS THAT ARE MIDDLE TO BOTTOM
AND THE SUCCESS THEY ARE HAVING.
KARL: THE CARDINALS GAVE UP FIVE
RUNS LATE AND LOST AGAIN.
RIGHT BACK UP THE MIDDLE.
FIELDED BY LEMAHIEU.
YOU CAN PUT HIM ANYWHERE ON THE
INFIELD.
HE WILL MAKE THE PLAY.
HERE COMES EDUARDO ESCOBAR.
7-UP, SEVEN DOWN SO FAR FOR
GERRIT COLE.
EDUARDO: HE HAS BEEN DOING IT
WITH THE FASTBALL.
IT HAS WORKED FOR HIM.
KARL: ESCOBAR HAS BEEN GOOD WHEN
HE HAS PLAYED.
THAT ONE WAS A LITTLE TOO HIGH.
THREE HOME RUNS IN HIS LAST 21
GAMES.
A HANDFUL OF DOUBLES.
DAVID: FRAMING THAT PITCH AND
BRINGING IT DOWN THE ZONE.
KARL: BIG SWING AND A MISS.
96.
DAVID: YOU DO NOT THINK THERE IS
FLOPPING IN BASEBALL, CATCHER
FRAMING IS FLOPPING.
WATCH HIS MITT.
KARL: NO ONE HAS MADE ANY
CONTACT WITH HIS FASTBALL.
HE IS THROWING UNTIL SOMEONE
DOES.
DAVID: CONFIDENCE AND
CONVICTION.
THE CARRY ON IT IS DIFFERENT.
THE WAY IT JUMPS.
VELOCITY CAN BE MISLEADING AT
TIMES.
THAT IS WHY WE KEEP TRACK OF
EVERYTHING ELSE.
KARL: HE IS PITCHING AS WELL AS
HE HAS ALL NIGHT.
EDUARDO: THIS IS A TOUGH START.
IN ORDER FOR HIM TO BE ABLE TO
HIT GERRIT COLE, HE HAS TO FORCE
HIM TO COME DOWN.
HE WAS NOT ABLE TO DO IT IN THAT
SWING.
NOW HE HAS TO PLAY DEFENSE WITH
THE BAT.
DAVID: IT IS VERY OLD-SCHOOL
STYLISTICALLY.
KARL: HE MISSES BADLY.
GERRIT COLE IS DEALING WITH AN
UMPIRE WHO HAS A REPUTATION FOR
A PITCHER FRIENDLY STRIKE ZONE.
SLOWED CHOPPER.
THAT WILL BE A TOUGH ONE.
NOT A PROBLEM FOR GERRIT COLE.
NO PROBLEMS SO FAR.
NINE UP, NINE DOWN.
KARL: THE RED SOX TRYING TO
DEFEND FENWAY AGAINST THE
YANKEES.
WE WILL HAVE THE CALL.
STANTON SWINGS AT THE FIRST ONE.
THIS ONE WILL GET INTO THE
SEATS.
I WANT TO THANK THE 2 MILLION
VIEWERS WHO TUNED IN.
HOPING FOR A SIMILAR NUMBER,
MAYBE A LITTLE HIGHER.
FATHER‘S DAY WEEKEND AT FENWAY
PARK.
STANTON RECOGNIZED THAT PITCH
AND FOULS IT STRAIGHT BACK.
EDUARDO: SHE HAS BEEN WAITING
FOR THIS.
KARL: YOU ARE RIGHT.
SUNDAY NIGHT IS NOT ENOUGH.
SHE WOULD JUST AS SOON DO IT
EVERY NIGHT.
ALL BASEBALL, ALL OF THE TIME.
A GOOD LOOK AT THE FRAMING OF
ALVAREZ.
RIGHT NOW HE IS TOP FIVE IN
FRAMING AND BLOCKING.
HE GOT STANTON.
A HIGH SLIDER.
DAVID: IT HAS BEEN THE FEATURE
PITCH ALL NIGHT.
WE SAW MORE OF THIS THAN ANY
OTHER PITCH.
HE GOT STANTON TO MISS IT.
EDUARDO: SOMETIMES AS A HITTER
YOU SEE IT IN YOU THINK IT WILL
BREAK A LITTLE BIT MORE THAN
WHAT IT DOES.
IT DID NOT.
KARL: VERLANDER GETTING A LITTLE
FILTHY HERE.
THAT WAS A CURVEBALL.
EDUARDO: IT HAS BEEN CURVEBALLS
AND SLIDERS.
KARL: AS A HITTER, YOU SEE
FASTBALL UP, IF YOU DO NOT LIKE
IT, DO YOU ASSUME IT IS A
FASTBALL?
EDUARDO: ABSOLUTELY.
THAT IS WHY THE CUREVBALL WORKS
WELL.
KARL: THIS IS A TOUGH ONE.
LOOK WHAT I FOUND?
VIENTOS SCREWED -- STOOP IT UP
OUT OF THE DIRT.
EDUARDO: OVER THE TOP.
THAT IS WHAT MAKES IT EASIER FOR
VIENTOS TO BE ABLE TO GET IT.
EASIER FOR A FIRST BASEMAN.
BEAUTIFULLY DIGS THIS OUT.
KARL: THERE IS A GRACED -- GREAT
SECURITY IN A FIRST BASEMAN‘S
GLOVE.
VERLANDER FALLS BEHIND 2-0.
MARK CANHA LAST NIGHT, VIENTOS
TONIGHT AT FIRST BASE.
WE SAW PETE ALONSO IN THE LOCKER
ROOM BEFORE THE GAME.
WE HAD A GOOD CONVERSATION WITH
HIM.
HE SEEMS TO BE GETTING BETTER.
NO TIMETABLE.
EDUARDO: GOOD PRESENCE OF MIND.
DAVID: EVERY OUT AS A HOT
COMMODITY FOR JUSTIN VERLANDER.
YOU SEE HIS REACTION RIGHT
THERE.
KARL: DID IN THE AMOUNT OF
PICTURES USED LAST NIGHT AND IN
SOME CASES THEY ARE BEING USED
THREE TIMES IN FOUR NIGHTS, THE
STARTERS NEED TO GO DEEP.
DAVID: HE PULLED A DIRTY TRICK
ON ME.
HE PUSHED MY BUTTON.
HE CUT ME OFF.
THAT IS A DIRTY TRICK.
HE MUTED ME.
KARL: LEFT FIELD.
PHAM TO HIS RIGHT.
HE IS THERE TO MAKE THE PLAY.
VERLANDER HAS GOTTEN THROUGH
FOUR.
KEVIN: JOSE BERRIOS WORKING ON A
NO-HITTER.
SIX INNINGS, FOUR STRIKEOUTS,
JUST ONE WALK.
ADLEY RUTSCHMAN HAS JUST BROKEN
IT UP.
THE NO-HITTER IS OVER.
KARL: THE LATEST UPDATE.
ADLEY RUTSCHMAN DELIVERS THE HIT
THAT INS -- ENDS THE NO-HIT
NIGHT.
GERRIT COLE, 97 ON THAT
FASTBALL.
BOTH OF THESE PITCHERS HAVE A
VERY HIGH PERCENTAGE OF STRIKES.
COLE STRUCK OUT NIMMO HIS FIRST
TIME UP.
HE MISSES IN THE DIRT.
DAVID: WE HAVE OUR PITCHER‘S
DUEL SO FAR.
KARL: BUT DIFFERENT STYLES.
DAVID: VERLANDER REALLY
ESTABLISHING THE SLIDER.
YOU HAVE TO GIVE THEM A LOT OF
CREDIT.
HE IS GOING ABOUT IT IN A
DIFFERENT WAY.
KARL: YOU MENTIONED THE FACT
THAT COLE HAD NOT GIVEN UP ANY
HOME RUNS IN HIS FIRST SEVEN
STARTS.
IN A GAME LIKE THIS, ONE SWING
CAN CHANGE EVERYTHING.
NIMMO WENT YARD LAST NIGHT.
EDUARDO: ALMOST GOT HIT BY A
PITCH ON THAT ELBOW PAD
YESTERDAY.
NOT AFRAID TO KEEP IT IN THERE.
KARL: WE HAD HIM WHERE THE
MICROPHONE EARLY THIS SEASON.
HE GREW UP IN WYOMING.
HE SAID YOU HAVE TO GET THROWN
OFF OF AN ANIMAL.
THIS ONE SLAPPED INTO LEFT
FIELD.
GOOD TO KNOW HE IS WITH US ON
WEDNESDAYS AS WELL.
EDUARDO: THAT GUIDE PARTIES
EVERY NIGHT.
UP IN THE AIR.
KARL: COLE HAS 10 OF THE FIRST
10 AS HE BOUNCES WANT TO
STARLING MARTE.
NOW THEY ARE TEAMMATES.
BILL MILLER SAID HE DID NOT NEED
TO GET OUT OF THE WAY.
THAT WAS A STRIKE.
YOU SEE THE BODY LANGUAGE AND
THE HEAD SHAKING FROM MARTE.
1-2.
DAVID: SEEING THOSE KIND OF
SWINGS OFF OF A FASTBALL.
THAT TELLS YOU ALL YOU NEED TO
KNOW ABOUT HIS STUFF TONIGHT.
97 MILES PER HOUR.
EMERGENCY HACK.
KARL: HAPPY TO FOUL IT OFF.
RIZZO FIRES A PERFECT THROW.
EDUARDO: YOU HAVE TO LOVE THAT
IF YOU ARE ANTHONY RIZZO.
YOUR PITCHER GOES OVER TO FIRST.
THE VETERAN PITCHER GETS OVER.
DAVID: HE GAVE HIM A HEATER.
KARL: YOU SEE THE SMILE ON HIS
FACE.
EDUARDO: THAT THAT -- BAT WAS
SOLID OFF -- SAWED OFF.
GOOD ACTION ON THE HEATER.
KARL: DONALDSON IS OUT OF ROOM.
EDUARDO: HE IS ALREADY CHOKED
UP.
DAVID: WHERE IS RIZZO GOING?
KARL: 0-2.
HE HAD A TERRIFIC AT-BAT LAST
NIGHT.
LEMAHIEU WAS PLAYING THIRD BASE.
HE SLAPPED IT DOWN THE
THIRD-BASE LINE AND ENDED UP
SCORING A COUPLE.
SHE IS GONE.
COLE IS ROLLING.
MCNEIL PUNCHED OUT.
THIS IS A PITCHER‘S DUEL.
THE KNUCKLE CURVE SHOWS UP TO
GET MCNEIL.
KARL: THIS IS YOUR NIGHT TO
SHINE.
VERLANDER AND COLE,
FOUR PERFECT INNINGS.
A HUGE CROWD ON A SUBWAY SERIES
NIGHT AT CITI FIELD.
VERLANDER DELIVERS.
HE GETS THE CALLED STRIKE ONE.
A DOUBLE HAS BEEN THE ONLY HIT
OF THE GAME SO FAR.
DAVID: VERLANDER HAS A SHARP
SLIDER TONIGHT.
IT HAS INDUCED SIX SWING IN THIS
IS.
THERE IS YOUR CONTRASTING
STYLES.
KARL: ARE WE LOOKING AT WHAT HE
MIGHT BE EIGHT YEARS FROM NOW?
IS THIS THE EVOLUTION OF WHAT
GERRIT COLE MIGHT SOMEDAY
BECOME?
DAVID: YES.
WHEN YOU DON‘T HAVE THE GOOD
HIGH FASTBALL, YOU NEED TO SPOT
IT MORE EAST AND WEST.
LIKE WE JUST SAW.
AND YOU NEED TO DELIVER --
DEVELOP YOUR SLIDER.
KARL: LINDOR STAYS DOWN.
A SHORT HOP THROW.
VIENTOS BAILS HIM OUT.
KEVIN: THE ANGELS JUST FOUR
POINT FIVE GAMES OUT AND TRYING
TO SLICE INTO THAT.
ANTHONY RENDON INTO NO MAN‘S
LAND.
IT WILL DROP IN.
THE ANGELS LEAD 1-0.
KARL: TROUT BEARING DOWN ON THE.
THE BALL IS COMING IN.
IT‘S THE ANGELS AND PHIL NEVIN
WHO WAS WITH AARON BOONE IN NEW
YORK FOR SO LONG.
DOING A GOOD JOB IN ANAHEIM.
ISIAH KINER-FALEFA CHECKS IS
SWINGING.
NO SWING ACCORDING TO THE FIRST
BASEMAN.
-- FIRST BASE UMPIRE.
EDUARDO: AS SOON AS LINDOR
STANDS STRAIGHT UP, HE DID NOT
HAVE MUCH ON THE THROW.
HE SAID MY BAD ON THAT ONE BUT
THANK YOU FOR PICKING ME UP.
NICE JOB OVER THERE.
MARK CANHA HAS PLAYED A NICE
FIRST BASE AS WELL.
KARL: GETS THE CALL.
DAVID: YOU SEE THE BREAKDOWN.
PITCHING OFF OF HIS SLIDER.
MORE SLIDERS THAN ANY OTHER
PITCH.
AND IT IS A GOOD ONE TONIGHT.
KARL: HE CHALLENGED
KINER-FALEFA.
FOUL TIP INTO THE GLOVE OF
ALVAREZ.
EDUARDO: JUST LETTING US KNOW HE
HAS IT IN HIS BACK POCKET WHEN
HE NEEDS IT.
DAVID: THE BEST ONE HE HAS
THROWN TONIGHT.
YOU SEE THE LIFE ON THAT PITCH.
COMING RIGHT AT YOU.
NO DEVIATION.
JUST COULD CARRY RIGHT KARL:
KARL: THROUGH THE GLOVE.
HE HAS RETIRED EIGHT IN A ROW.
THIS IS THE GUY DID NOT RETIRE.
HE SWINGS AT THE FIRST ONE.
THAT IS A CONFIDENT SWING FROM
BILLY MCKINNEY.
HE HIT NINE HOME RUNS IN THE
MINORS.
LOCKED HIM UP WITH A VERY GOOD
CURVEBALL.
DAVID: YOU BRING UP A GOOD
POINT.
HE WAS NOT ON THE ROSTER.
HE REALLY HAD TO HIM REST THE
YANKEES.
KARL: FIVE PUNCH-OUTS FOUR
VERLANDER SO FAR.
THAT ONE NEARLY HIT MCKINNEY.
THERE HAVE BEEN A NUMBER OF
INJURIES OVER THE CAREER OF
JUSTIN VERLANDER.
TOMMY JOHN A COUPLE OF YEARS
AGO.
BUT HE IN TERRIFIC SHAPE.
GRINDING IT HERE.
AT 40 YEARS OLD.
DAVID: REALLY IMPRESSED WITH THE
ADJUSTMENTS HE HAS MADE TONIGHT.
SOME VINTAGE VERLANDER.
ESTABLISHING HIS SLIDER AND
THROWING IT OFTEN.
THAT HAS BEEN THE KEY TO HIS
SUCCESS.
KARL: TAKE A LOOK AT WHAT JUSTIN
VERLANDER HAS BEEN ABLE TO
ACCOMPLISH WHEN HE HAS BEEN ON
THE MOUND.
AS FAR AS CY YOUNG BOATS.
AND WHERE HE HAS FINISHED.
GERRIT COLE HAS GOTTEN A BUNCH
OF VOTES.
JUST DOESN‘T HAVE THE AWARD YET.
DAVID: IT IS VERY RARE THAT ONE
PLAYER IS TRADED IN A TRADE
DEADLINE AND A BALANCE IS --
SHIFTS THE BALANCE OF POWER.
THAT IS WHAT HAPPENED WITH
JUSTIN VERLANDER WHEN HE WAS
TRADED FROM THE TIGERS TO THE
ASTROS.
KARL: THERE YOU GO.
HE WILL WALK OFF THE MOUND
FEELING VERY GOOD ABOUT HIMSELF.
SIX STRIKEOUTS.
KARL: DEFINITION OF A PITCHER‘S
DUEL, WE HAVE ONE HERE BETWEEN
VERLANDER AND COLE.
SIX PUNCH-OUTS FOR VERLANDER.
COLE WITH FIVE.
HE WILL GET LINDOR, ALVAREZ AND
BRETT BATY.
VERLANDER IS PITCH COUNT IS 84.
COLE AND EFFICIENT 57.
THE GUARDS -- THE GUYS AVAILABLE
TONIGHT ARE ABOUT THE GUYS WHO
GOT THEM THE BULLPEN REPUTATION
AND CREDIBILITY.
LINDOR HITS IT TO RIZZO.
COLE COVERS.
96 MILES PER HOUR.
WHEN HE FACED ANOTHER GUY WHO
HAD SIMILAR CREDIBILITY THAT YOU
DID, WHAT IMPACT DID THAT HAVE
ON YOU AS YOU GOT INTO THE GAME?
DAVID: WHEN THEY ARE THROWING
WELL YOU NOTICE.
KARL: LINDOR HITS IT HARD
TOWARDS THE GAP.
KINER-FALEFA GOING BACK.
IT‘S OFF THE WALL.
LINDOR BREAKS UP COLE‘S PERFECT
NIGHT WITH A LEADOFF DOUBLE.
EDUARDO: EXIT VELOCITY 105.
THIS WAS A BREAKING PITCH 80
MPH, HUNG DOWN THE MIDDLE.
TREVINO IS REACHING TOWARDS HIS
RIGHT TO GET IT.
RIGHT IN LINDOR‘S WHEELHOUSE.
HITS IT HARD AND HE NEEDS TO
START SWINGING WELL FROM THE
LEFT SIDE AND HE DOES JUST THAT.
KARL: PASSED BALLS TO ALVAREZ
HIS FIRST TIME OUT, HE STRUCK
OUT.
STARTS HIM UP WITH A BREAKING
PITCH, THE SLIDER TO GET AHEAD.
BIG SPOT FOR THE ROOKIE CATCHER.
PUTS THIS ONE INTO RIGHT, FAIRLY
DEEP.
BAUERS IS AT THE WALL AND MAKES
THE PLAY.
NICE RUNNING CATCH BY BAUERS.
LINDOR GETS TO THIRD BUT HE WENT
A LONG WAY.
EDUARDO: TREVINO IN THE THIRD
INNING COULDN‘T GET MCKINNEY
OVER.
WITH NO OUTS.
ON THIS ONE YOU SEE HIM TRYING
TO GO THE OTHER WAY, TRADING
PLACES WITH LINDOR, GETS IT DEEP
ENOUGH AND FAR ENOUGH TO MOVE
LINDOR OVER TO THIRD.
THAT WILL FORCE THE INFIELD TO
COME IN,.
KARL: AFFECTIONATELY KNOWN AS
THE BABY METS, AND THE CHANCE OF
-- CHANTS OF BATY.
UP ON NATIONALS, JOSÉ ABREU
HITTING .3 O4 IN THE MONTH OF
JUNE.
12 R.B.I., TIED FOR THE MOST IN
THE AMERICAN LEAGUE.
FRAMBER VALDEZ, THREE SCORELESS,
2-0 IN THE FOURTH.
KARL: HERE WE GO WITH BRETT
BATY.
ALVAREZ MOVES LINDOR TO THIRD.
INFIELD IN ON THE GRASS.
BIG SWING AS COLE THREW 98 BY
HIM.
EDUARDO: THEY HAVE BEEN POUNDING
BATY IN DURING THE SUBWAY
SERIES.
MCKINNEY HAS TO PLAY SHALLOWER
IN LEFT FIELD.
KARL: 0-2.
EDUARDO: GOT TO PROTECT FROM THE
JAM SHOT.
GERRIT COLE NEEDS TO EXECUTE THE
PITCH.
IF HE DOESN‘T GET THE SWING AND
MISS, IT SHOULDN‘T BE A BARREL
SHOT OPPOSITE FIELD.
KARL: SLIDER IN THE DIRT.
TREVINO HAS BEEN TERRIFIC
BLOCKING EVERYTHING BUT BE
CAREFUL WITH LINDOR AT THIRD.
THE 0-2 GOES RIGHT BY HIM, 98
MILES AN HOUR.
HUGE STRIKEOUT FOR THE SECOND
OUT OF THE INNING.
SIXTH OF THE NIGHT FOR COLE.
DAVID: COLE SHOWED WHO IS
DRIVING THE BUS.
SHAKES OFF TWICE ON AN 0-2
PITCH.
THEN THAT ONE SAILED RIGHT ON
BY.
TREVINO WANTED A SLIDER OR
CURVEBALL.
COLE SAID NO, I WANT THIS ONE.
KARL: NOW TOMMY PHAM, WHO HAS
BEEN GOOD FOR THE METS.
LOOKS AT 99 RIGHT DOWN BROADWAY.
THIS ONE IS RIFLED TO RIGHT
FIELD.
BAUERS GOING BACK, HE WILL NOT
GET IT.
TOMMY PHAM DELIVERS A DOUBLE.
THAT PLATES LINDOR.
IT IS 1-0 METS.
EDUARDO: THERE HASN‘T BEEN A
FASTBALL TOMMY PHAM HASN‘T LIKED
IN HIS ENTIRE BIG-LEAGUE CAREER.
OUT OVER THE PLATE, THE REACTION
OF GERRIT COLE, HE KNEW IT AS
SOON AS HE HIT IT.
HE KNEW THAT BAUERS WOULD
STRUGGLE TO GET TO THIS ONE.
DAVID: TOMMY PHAM CAN HIT THE
BALL HARD.
KARL: HE HAS BEEN SO GOOD IN A
YEAR IN WHICH THE OFFENSE HASN‘T
BEEN GREAT.
PHAM COMES THROUGH, PICKING UP
HIS 23RD R.B.I.
A DIFFERENT HITTER THIS YEAR.
TREVINO SAW PHAM OFF THE BAG AT
SECOND AND CAME UP READY TO
THROW DOWN TO VOLPE BUT IT GOT
OUT OF HIS GLOVE.
EDUARDO: GOOD HARD SECONDARY
SLICE.
LINDOR TAKING SECOND AND NOW
PHAM AT SECOND.
KARL: VERLANDER GAVE UP A DOUBLE
AND GOT THE NEXT THREE.
COLE GAVE UP THE DOUBLE TO
LINDOR AND GOT THE NEXT TWO,
THEN PHAM GOT HIM.
1-0.
HERE IS ESCOBAR.
OFF THE PLATE.
ONE BALL, ONE STRIKE.
DAVID: YOU CAN SEE VOLPE THE
SHORTSTOP LISTENING IN HIS EAR
FOR THE PITCH SELECTION FROM
PITCHCOM, AS WELL.
KARL: IN THERE FOR A STRIKE.
WATCH BAUERS GOES BACK AND
OBVIOUSLY THERE IS THE WALL
RIGHT WHERE THE BALL LANDED.
THAT IS A HOME RUN NOT PHAM --
THAT PHAM WOUND UP ON SECOND
WITH, IN FOUR OTHER BALLPARKS.
COLE WILL STRAND THE RUNNER AT
SECOND, BUT SOME DAMAGE DONE
TONIGHT OFF THE BAT OF LINDOR,
WHO RELEASES A HUGE SHOE TODAY
AND GOT A CHANCE TO RUN TO
SECOND, THEN RUN HOME AFTER PHAM
WENT TO RIGHT.
COLE IS NOT HAPPY.
IT IS 1-0.
KARL: NINTH DOUBLE OF THE YEAR
FOR TOMMY PHAM PLATES FRANCISCO
LINDOR.
VERLANDER STARTS THIS HALF
INNING OFF, TREVINO, WITH A
BREAKING PITCH.
THE ONLY GUY WHO HAS A HIT,
MCKINNEY WITH A DOUBLE.
VERLANDER COMING OFF BACK TO
BACK PUNCH-OUTS TO END THE FIFTH
INNING.
HE HAS A HALF DOZEN OF THOSE, 86
PITCHES.
EDUARDO: JOSÉ TREVINO, HOW HAPPY
IS HE WITH ORAL ROBERTS AND THE
COLLEGE WORLD SERIES?
KARL: I TALKED TO HIM ABOUT
THAT.
AND PETE ALONSO THE FLORIDA
SCOUTING REPORT DOWN.
FOULED.
COLLEGE WORLD SERIES STARTS
FRIDAY.
EIGHT TEAMS.
IN OMAHA, NEBRASKA.
BIG-NAME PROGRAMS, YOU MENTIONED
ORAL ROBERTS WITH 51 WINS.
LSU ACCORDING TO KILEY
MCDANIEL‘S HAS MORE PROSPECTS ON
THEIR TEAM THEN SEVERAL MAJOR
LEAGUE TEAMS AND THEIR FARM
SYSTEMS.
WHICH SHOULD BE EXCITING.
COLLEGE WORLD SERIES STARTS
FRIDAY ON ESPN.
DAY AND NIGHT GAMES.
EDUARDO: BEST SHOW ON TURF.
KARL: 2-2.
EDUARDO: YOU HAVE NEVER BEEN TO
OMAHA?
DAVID: I WAS PLAYING MINOR
LEAGUE BALL IN OMAHA AND HAD TO
LEAVE TOWN DURING THAT TIME.
WE HAD TO GO ON A ROAD TRIP TO
ACCOMMODATE THE KARL WORLD
SERIES -- THE COLLEGE WORLD
SERIES.
KARL: THAT IS A FAIR BALL FOR
TREVINO.
CHASED INTO THE CORNER AND
TREVINO DOUBLES.
THE FOURTH HIT OF THE GAME.
TREVINO WITH A LEADOFF DOUBLE.
DAVID: ANOTHER CURVEBALL STAYING
RIGHT THERE.
I THOUGHT VERLANDER THREW A
STRIKE WITH ONE OF THOSE TWO
PITCHES AGO AND DIDN‘T GET THE
CALL.
THIS ONE STAYS UP JUST ENOUGH
FOR TREVINO TO LAY SIT DOWN THE
LINE -- LACE IT DOWN THE LINE.
UNLUCKY FOR VERLANDER BUT GOOD
JOB BY TREVINO TAKING ADVANTAGE
OF THAT LAST ONE.
KARL: CRITICAL INNING AFTER YOU
GET THE LEAD TO COME OUT AND PUT
A ZERO UP.
HERE IS VOLPE.
EDUARDO: THIS IS VOLPE‘S JOB.
HE HAS TO BE ABLE TO MOVE
TREVINO TO THIRD BASE.
DAVID: HERE IS THE PITCH I WAS
TALKING ABOUT.
WATCH THE FRAME.
LOOKED LIKE ALVAREZ GOT FOOLED.
DIDN‘T GET A GOOD FRAME ON THAT.
THAT WAS IN THE BOX WITHOUT A
DOUBT.
SOMETIMES THOSE BIG BREAK AND
CURVEBALLS ARE HARD TO CATCH.
KARL: 1-1 TO VOLPE.
GOOD CURVEBALL, ONE BALL, TWO
STRIKES.
EDUARDO: THE TWO BREAKING
PITCHES, DOES NOT SEEM LIKE
THERE IS ANY SENSE TO BEING ABLE
TO TRADE PLACES WITH TREVINO THE
OTHER WAY.
WITH TWO STRIKES YOU HAVE TO PUT
THE BALL IN PLAY, FORCE THE
DEFENSE.
KARL: JUST FOULS IT OFF.
WENT BACK TO THE CURVEBALL
AGAIN.
THAT IS ALL HE HAS SEEN IN THIS
AT-BAT.
DAVID: VERLANDER IS BREAKING
BALL PACKAGES TONIGHT HAVE BEEN
OUTSTANDING.
SLIDER-CURVEBALL COMBINATION HAS
GIVEN METS FANS A ROADMAP TO HOW
HE CAN CONTINUE TO BE
SUCCESSFUL.
AND BE PATIENT WITH THE FASTBALL
AS IT IMPROVES.
KARL: A COUPLE 95‘S IN THE LAST
HALF INNING.
EDUARDO: ALVAREZ WAS ASKING FOR
THE PITCH UP.
KARL: AT HOME YOU DON‘T USUALLY
GET THE BOOS WHEN THE HOME
PITCHER STEPS OFF BUT THERE ARE
YANKEE FANS AT CITI FIELD
TONIGHT.
1-2.
HIGH.
EDUARDO: PERFECT PITCH, ELEVATED
.
MESSING WITH THE DEPTH
PERCEPTION.
GOES RIGHT BACK TO THE CURVEBALL
OR THE SLIDER.
KARL: THERE IS STIRRING IN THE
METS BULLPEN.
ANOTHER ONE HIGH AT 96.
EDUARDO: EARLY IN THE COUNT,
LINDOR WAS PLAYING BEHIND
TREVINO BUT NOW, IT IS MCNEIL
TRYING TO KEEP IT CLOSE.
NO ATTEMPT AT ALL AT HITTING THE
BALL THE OTHER WAY.
KARL: THERE IT IS.
HIT IT THE OTHER WAY.
MARTE GOOD ARM, HE WILL RUN ON
HIM, HERE IS THE THROW.
A LITTLE HIGH AND IT GETS PAST
ESCOBAR.
EDUARDO: I WAS SURPRISED HE TOOK
OFF AND WENT TO THIRD.
HE OVERTHROWS BUT WE HAVE SEEN
MARTE WITH THE GREAT ARM FROM
RIGHT FIELD MAKE SPECTACULAR
THROWS.
GETS BEHIND HIM, LETS IT GO.
TOO MUCH LOFT ON IT.
BUT HE WAS GOING RIGHT TO THIRD.
WE ARE FORTUNATE THE BALL HIT
THE RAILING AND DIDN‘T GO INTO
THE DUGOUT.
KARL: THE METS BRING THE INFIELD
IN.
HERE IS BAUERS, LEADOFF HITTER
FOR THE YANKEES.
HE HAS SEEN A TON OF PITCHES
FROM VERLANDER TONIGHT.
THIRD TIME BAUERS HAS SEEN
VERLANDER.
EDUARDO: HE HAS A BACKUP, HAD TO
RUN TO GET THE BASEBALL.
WITH THE TIMECLOCK IT SPEEDS UP.
DAVID: FIVE MOUND VISITS LEFT
FOR THE METS.
KARL: HE MISSES IN AT 96.
JEFF GRAHAM IS GETTING LOOSE IN
THE METS BULLPEN.
VERLANDER HAS THROWN 100
PITCHES.
2-0 TO BAUERS WHO HAS NOW SEEN
22 PITCHES FROM VERLANDER.
FEELS LIKE THAT MEANS A
CONVERSATION, WHATEVER THE
CONCLUSION OF THIS PLATE
APPEARANCE IS.
EDUARDO: EXCELLENT ADJUSTMENT BY
VOLPE TO DRIVE THE BALL TO
RIGHT, FORCING THE METS TO MAKE
A PLAY.
KARL: 3-0, GREEN LIGHT FOR
BAUERS.
THREW HIM A SLIDER UP IN THE
ZONE.
EDUARDO: I LIKE THAT BOONE GAVE
HIM THE GREEN LIGHT.
ONE OF THE BETTER AT-BATS
AGAINST VERLANDER EVEN THOUGH HE
DOESN‘T HAVE A HIT TO SHOW FOR
IT.
DAVID: AND TOOK A SWING AT THE
HIGH SLIDER.
KARL: TWO FLY OUTS TO RIGHT.
NOT A FAST RUNNER AT THIRD.
BUT BAUERS DELIVERS THE CLUTCH
R.B.I..
HOW GOOD HAS HE BEEN FOR THE
YANKEES?
IT IS NOW A 1-1 GAME IN THE
SIXTH.
EDUARDO: I DON‘T KNOW WHY THEY
HAVEN‘T GONE OUT TO TALK TO
VERLANDER.
OVER 100 PITCHES.
THIRD TIME BAUERS SEES
VERLANDER.
YOU WANT TO GIVE HIM A BREATHER
AFTER HE BACKS UP THIRD.
NOW LINDOR AND ALVAREZ ARE
HAVING A CONVERSATION WITH
VERLANDER.
DAVID: STANTON‘S PRESENCE FORCED
VERLANDER TO GO AFTER BAUERS,
THE RESPECT FOR STANTON.
KARL: WITH ALL THOSE MOUND
VISITS AVAILABLE, VERLANDER
HAVING TO BACK UP THIRD BASE,
LEADOFF DOUBLE BY TREVINO PLATED
BY BAUERS.
ONE DOWN IN THE SIXTH.
STANTON HAS STRUCK OUT TWICE.
THE FIRST PITCH IS IN THE DIRT.
DIFFERENT CIRCUMSTANCE FROM LAST
NIGHT WHEN THE METS GAVE
SCHERZER A BIG LEAD.
TONIGHT VERLANDER HAD A ONE RUN
LEAD AND HE COULDN‘T PROTECT IT
FOR HALF AN INNING.
THAT ONE IS DOWN.
EDUARDO: THE ABILITY OF TREVINO
AND VOLPE TO GET ON BASE,
TREVINO GETTING ON BASE WITH A
TWO STRIKE DOUBLE, THEN VOLPE
TWO STRIKE FLY OUT TO RIGHT.
ONE OF THE BIG REASONS VERLANDER
IS IN THE SITUATION RIGHT NOW.
KARL: TENUOUS.
105 PITCHES.
STANTON KILLS IT AT CITI FIELD.
HE IS LIKELY TO GET A GREEN
LIGHT ON 3-0.
THAT IS A HARD ONE.
ESCOBAR WILL GO TO SECOND.
MCNEIL.
JEFF MCNEIL ABLE TO TURN THE
DOUBLE PLAY TO GET STANTON AND
END THE INNING.
HOW ABOUT THE SQUIRREL?
EDUARDO: THAT BALL WAS SCALDED.
JEFF MCNEIL.
THAT MAN RIGHT THERE, LOVING
KARL: BACK TO SQUARE ONE.
1-1, BOTTOM SIX, DYNAMITE
DEFENSIVE PLAY BY THE METS.
THERE IS A ROCKET.
THEY ARE HITTING THE BALL HARD.
VIENTOS, THAT WAS 114 MPH AND
THAT WAS NOTHING COMPARED TO
STANTON, 108 L PROPER MUSCLE.
-- MILE PER HOUR MISSILE.
EDUARDO: GREAT PLAY BY ESCOBAR
AND THAT ONE THERE, MAKE DEAL
TURNING IT -- MCNEIL, TURNING
IT, UNDERSTANDING STANTON CAN‘T
BE ALLOWED THE BAG.
KARL: THE LEADOFF HITTERS HAVE
DONE THEIR JOB TONIGHT.
BAUERS DELIVERS THE R.B.I..
NUMERAL HAS SEEN 17 PITCHES --
NIMMO HAS SEEN 17 PITCHES.
TREVINO THOUGHT ABOUT THROWING
DOWN.
DAVID: WITH CATCHERS, WHEN YOU
COME UP WITH THAT YOU WILL NOT
GET A CALL.
THAT ONE, JUST A SLIVER.
KARL: TWO BALLS AND A STRIKE.
GREAT GAME TONIGHT.
1-1.
DOUBLES HAVE BEEN THE STORY.
FOUR DOUBLES SO FAR.
BAUERS HAD THE SINGLE TO KNOCK
IN A RUN.
VERLANDER WATCHES ON AS NIMMO
FOULS IT OFF.
HE GOT HIS FOOT.
THAT HAD TO HURT A LITTLE BIT.
DAVID: NEW YORK CITY DOESN‘T
NEED ANOTHER TOE STORY.
VIOLENT SLIDER DOWN AND IN.
KARL: UPPER LEFT PART OF HIS
KNEECAP.
DAVID: THAT‘S HARD TO DO.
KARL: NEARLY DID IT AGAIN
EDUARDO: BOTTOM OF THE SIXTH
INNING.
DAVID: THE FORMER RED SOX
OUTFIELDER DESCRIBED MARIANO
RIVERA‘S CUTTER AS VIOLENT.
WE HAVE SEEN SOME VIOLENT
PITCHES TONIGHT FROM BOTH SIDES.
KARL: 2-2.
NIMMO SINCE THIS BACK TO HOME
PLATE.
-- SENDS THIS BACK TO HOME
KARL: AS THE GAME WEARS ON, THE
MIDDLE INNINGS WHERE COLE WAS
THROWING IT, 80 PITCHES ON A
WARM NIGHT IN NEW YORK, IT IS
TAKING ITS TOLL A LITTLE.
DAVID: THINGS SLOW DOWN WHEN THE
LEADOFF MAN GETS ON.
KARL: NIMMO HITS THIS HARD.
VIENTOS WASN‘T SURE WHERE BAUERS
WAS AND SO HE IS CAREFUL.
IT IS FIRST AND SECOND, NOBODY
OUT.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
THIS DEEP INTO THE SEASON FOR
THE FIRST TIME COME UP 5-1 ON
THE CUBS.
AUSTIN HEDGES, ANDREW MCCUTCHEN,
SANTANA HAVE HOMERED.
PITTSBURGH TRYING TO HOLD OFF
THE REDS.
MATT MCLAIN.
HOW MUCH EXCITEMENT IS THERE?
HE IS HITTING .331.
IT IS 7-1.
KARL: SO MUCH EXCITEMENT THAT
EDUARDO‘S MOM IS GOING BACK TO
CINCINNATI WHY?
EDUARDO: HALL OF FAME WEEKEND
BUT SHE SAID I NEED AN ELLY
PICTURE.
IF SHE SAYS SHE NEEDS A PICTURE
WITH SOMEONE, THAT SOMEONE HAS
SOMETHING GOING ON.
KARL: ELLY IS A BLUR ON THE
BASES WITH POWER.
CINCINNATI PLAYING WELL.
HOW ABOUT THOSE PLUCKY A‘S
WITH A WINNING STREAK?
STARLING MARTE, VIENTOS AT
SECOND AND NIMMO AT FIRST.
SWINGS AT ONE WAY OUTSIDE THE
ZONE.
0-1.
EDUARDO: LAST TIME UP, MARTE
BROKE HIS BAT.
SHATTERED HIS BAT ON A GROUND
BALL TO SECOND.
HE WAS TRYING TO CHEAT.
KARL: DONALDSON AND RIZZO IN ON
THE CORNERS.
WILL NOT GO FISHING FOR THAT
ONE.
EDUARDO: SORT OF PREDICTABLE.
DAVID: WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT
GERRIT COLE AND HOW HE
ESTABLISHES THE FASTBALL, KEPT
THROWING UNTIL THEY HIT IT.
NOW THE ADJUSTMENT PERIOD,
BREAKING OUT THE BREAKING
PITCHES.
KARL: WAY OUTSIDE.
VIENTOS SINGLED.
HAD THE HARDEST BATTED BALL OF
2023.
114 .9 OFF THE BAT, HARDEST HIT
BATTED BALL OF 23.
MARTE SENDS THAT OUT OF PLAY.
THE 118.3 WE SAW STANTON HIT ONE
TO THIRD BASE WAS THE HARDEST
HIT BATTED BALL VERLANDER HAS
ALLOWED UNDER STATCAST.
THAT WAS 2015.
WOUND UP IN A DOUBLE PLAY.
JIMMY CORDERO IS WARMING AND THE
YANKEES BULLPEN.
2-2 TO MARTE, WAY LATE ON THE
FASTBALL AT 99 ELEVATED.
GERRIT COLE PICKS UP STRIKEOUT
NUMBER EIGHT.
EDUARDO: IS THAT WHAT WE CALL
PITCHING BACKWARDS?
DAVID: THREE SLIDERS TO SET HIM
UP AND DO YOU THINK THIS GUY
RETAINS HIS VELOCITY OR REACHES
BACK FOR A LITTLE EXTRA AT
TIMES.
THERE IS YOUR PROOF, 99.
KARL: MARTE.
LINDOR STRUCK OUT LATE LAST
NIGHT WITH THE BASES LOADED.
GOES DOWN AGAIN TONIGHT.
HERE IS MCNEIL.
SLAPPED ONE DOWN THE THIRD-BASE
LINE LAST NIGHT FROM SIMILAR
SITUATION.
THAT WAS 99 AND THAT GOT A LOT
OF THE K ZONE.
COLE KNOWS IT.
FOR A GUY WHO HAS CALLED A LOT
OF STRIKES TONIGHT, THAT LOOKED
LIKE A BILL MILLER MISS.
WAY OUT IN FRONT OF THAT 90 MPH
CHANGEUP.
EDUARDO: WAS THAT HIS FIRST
CHANGEUP?
DAVID: FIRST CHANGEUP OF THE
GAME ON EITHER SIDE AND A GOOD
ONE BY GERRIT COLE.
KARL: ON HIS 88TH PITCH COME THE
FIRST CHANGEUP.
SO HE HAS GONE CHANGEUP.
JUST THREW A SLIDER.
DO YOU TRY TO BLOW ONE BY HIM UP
TOP?
DAVID: HE GOT MCNEIL LAST TIME
WITH THE KNUCKLE CURVE WAY IN
FRONT.
THAT IS PROBABLY IN HIS MIND.
GERRIT COLE COULD TRY THAT AGAIN
OR UP THE LADDER.
IF YOU ARE GOING TO GO HEATER,
YOU HAD BETTER GET HIM TO CHASE.
KARL: TERRIFIC BAT CONTROL.
AS DIFFICULT A GUY IN BASEBALL
TO STRIKE OUT.
HE WILL NOT GET IT HERE.
KINER-FALEFA MAKES THE EASY PLAY
IN CENTER.
HE GETS MARTE TO STRIKE OUT AND
MCNEIL TO FLY OUT.
HERE IS LINDOR.
CLAYTON KERSHAW IS GETTING SET,
WARMING UP, TERRIFIC NUMBERS.
KEEPS GOING AND GOING.
13 STARTS THIS SEASON.
LOS ANGELES, LOOKING UP AT THE
DIAMONDBACKS AND THE STANDINGS
OUT WEST.
KERSHAW GETS THE BALL AGAINST
THE WHITE SOX ON ESPN2.
IN ABOUT 35 MINUTES.
LINDOR DOUBLED HIS LAST TIME UP
ON ON OFF-SPEED PITCH.
THAT ONE WILL GET OUT OF PLAY.
EDUARDO: YOU SEE THE YANKEES A
LOT, A LOT MORE THAN WE DO.
ABREU IS WARMING UP IN THE
BULLPEN WITH THE NUMBER ONE ON
THE MOUND.
WHY?
DAVID: THAT IS CORDERO.
EDUARDO: C1
WHY IS HE WARMING UP?
DAVID: IF COLE GIVES IT UP HE
WANTS TO PROTECT HIM IF THE
PITCH COUNT GETS TOO HIGH.
CORDERO HAS BEEN VERY GOOD.
THE YANKEES BULLPEN HAS BEEN
GOOD THIS YEAR.
CORDERO IS YOUR GUY TO COME IN
WITH A HARD SINKER AND HARD
SLIDER TO FACE A TOUGH
RIGHT-HANDED BATTER.
MAYBE IF IT GETS TO TOMMY PHAM.
KARL: WHY DO YOU ASK THAT?
DO YOU THINK IT WOULD BOTHER A
PITCHER?
EDUARDO: IT IS THAT YOU EXPECT
TO HAVE MORE LEEWAY THAN THE
OTHERS.
WHEN CORDERO STARTED GETTING UP
HE WAS IN THE 70‘S WITH PITCHES.
KARL: 1-2 TO LINDOR.
HERE IT COMES.
HIGH.
EDUARDO: GO BACK TO THE VISIT ON
THE MOUND, GAVE HIM A BREATHER.
GERRIT COLE COULD STEP BACK AND
SAY I NEED TO GET AFTER MARTE.
HE DID.
MCNEIL FLIED OUT TO CENTER, NOW
FOCUSING ON FRANCISCO LINDOR.
KARL: 2-2.
RANGING INTO FOUL TERRITORY.
THERE IS ROOM.
DONALDSON IS AFTER IT AND GERRIT
COLE GETS OUT OF IT.
LEADOFF SINGLE FOR VIENTOS,
NIMMO FOLLOWED HIM AND THEN HE
GETS THREE AND A ROW.
KARL: TWO STARTERS WERE
OUTSTANDING TONIGHT.
VERLANDER NOW OUT OF THE GAME.
GERRIT COLE TBD.
THEY NEEDED TO GET OUTS AND THEY
DID.
1-1 GAME AS WE START THE
SEVENTH.
JEFF BRIGHAM I WANT TO PITCH FOR
THE METS AND THE FIRST PITCH HE
THROWS IS IN THERE FOR A STRIKE.
BRIGHAM APPEARED LAST NIGHT.
0.73 WHIP, SECOND LOWEST IN THE
MAJORS AMONG RELIEF PITCHERS WHO
MADE AT LEAST 20 APPEARANCES.
HIS 25TH GAME FOR BRIGHAM.
NO BALLS, TWO STRIKES.
DONALDSON, THEN RIZZO AND
LEMAHIEU.
HE WILL NOT CHASE.
INTERESTING SEASON FOR
VERLANDER.
THERE HAS BEEN GOOD AND BAD.
HIS NUMBERS AGAINST THE YANKEES
COMING IN WERE VERY GOOD
ESPECIALLY HIS LAST SIX STARTS.
HE DELIVERED A JAM TONIGHT.
-- A GEM TONIGHT.
DAVID: THE METS FAN BASE SHOULD
FEEL GOOD ABOUT WHAT THEY SAW
FROM VERLANDER.
HE SHOWED A ROADMAP FORWARD.
ALL THE TALK AROUND THE
FASTBALL, WE WERE TALKING ABOUT
THE MOVEMENT OF FILE ON THE
FOUR-SEAMER.
NOT THROWING AS HARD.
HE SHOWED YOU HOW TO GET TO PLAN
B, THEN THREW SOME GOOD
FASTBALLS LATER IN THE GAME.
A VERY ENCOURAGING EFFORT BY
VERLANDER.
HIS SLIDER WAS REALLY GOOD
TONIGHT, NO WALKS, SIX PUNCH
OUTS.
PITCHED OFF THE SLIDER EARLY,
THEN THREW SOME GOOD HEATERS
LATE.
KARL: DONALDSON, MATRIX MOVE TO
GET OUT OF THE WAY OF THAT.
3-2 FROM BRIGHAM.
THERE WE GO.
A WALK.
HAVEN‘T SEEN ANY OF THOSE
TONIGHT.
DAVID: THIS IS WHAT WE ARE
TALKING ABOUT.
90 MILE-PER-HOUR, SLIDERS UPPER
80‘S, CURVEBALLS IN THE 70‘S.
BACK AND FORTH PITCHING, FRONT
TO BACK AND LATER ON, VINTAGE
VERLANDER AT 96 AT THE TOP OF
THE ZONE.
VERY PATIENT, BROUGHT ALONG HIS
FASTBALL AND GOT IT LATE.
14 SWINGS AND MISSES.
LED BY THE SLIDER, EIGHT WHIFFS
ON THAT PITCH.
KARL: VERLANDER AND COLE HADN‘T
WALKED A BETTER.
BRIGHAM COMES IN AND WALKS
DONALDSON.
NO RIZZO.
-- NOW RIZZO.
HE HIT HIM.
TWO THINGS WE HAVEN‘T SEEN ALL
NIGHT.
BRIGHAM IS LOOKING FOR RIZZO TO
TRY TO GET OUT OF THE WAY.
I DON‘T THINK HE HAD A CHANCE TO
GET OUT OF THE WAY.
THAT WAS A HEATSEEKING PITCH.
EDUARDO: ANTHONY RIZZO DOESN‘T
GET OUT OF THE WAY.
THIS TIME GETS HIT ON THE LEFT
FOREHAND -- FOREARM.
A STRONGMAN THERE.
KARL: GETTING INTO THE MINDSET
OF A GUY WHO FOLLOWS VERLANDER
IN A TIGHT GAME, WITH THE
DEPLETED BULLPEN.
NO DREW SMITH, EJECTED LAST
NIGHT.
THEY CHECKED HIS HANDS, REASON
GIVEN, JUST TOO STICKY.
DIDN‘T HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY TO
CLEAN ANYTHING OFF SO NOW HE
WILL SERVE A SUSPENSION HE HAD
BUCK SHOWALTER IS DOWN A MAN IN
THE BULLPEN.
BRIGHAM HAS PUT HIMSELF IN A BAD
SPOT WITH A WALK AND A HIT
BATTER AND NOW LEMAHIEU.
EARLIER IN HIS CAREER, CERTAINLY
FOR THE YANKEES, MADE A LIVING
OUT OF DELIVERING IN THESE
SPOTS.
EDUARDO: THIS IS WHY LEMAHIEU IS
SO VALUABLE.
HE UNDERSTANDS TRYING TO FORCE
ESCOBAR IN A COUPLE MORE STEPS
UP THIRD BASE, STILL HAS THE
ABILITY TO DRIVE THE BALL TO
RIGHT AND NEEDS TO MOVE THE
RUNNER OVER.
KARL: MILLER CALLED THAT A
STRIKE.
0-1.
DAVID: HOME PLATE IS MOVING
AROUND A LITTLE BACK THERE
TONIGHT.
KARL: LEMAHIEU FOULS OFF THE
CUTTER AT 90.
YANKEES TRYING TO TAKE THE
SECOND OF THE TWO GAME SERIES
AND SWEEP THE QUICK SUBWAY
SERIES AGAINST THE METS.
DAVID: YOU WERE RIGHT, EDUARDO.
THE LOST ART OF PRODUCING A
PRODUCTIVE OUT.
WE WANT TO GET HITS WHEN YOU CAN
BUT SACRIFICING EXIT VELOCITY
FOR A PRODUCTIVE OUT TO THE
RIGHT SIDE SOMEWHERE, TRY TO
ADVANCE THE RUNNER OR BOTH
RUNNERS.
KARL: BROOKS RALEY IS UP FOR THE
METS.
1-2 SET UP OUTSIDE.
GREAT TAKE FROM LEMAHIEU AS IT
JUST MISSED THE STRIKE ZONE.
EDUARDO: WE ARE SEEING BETTER AT
BATS FROM DJ EARLY ON, LOTS OF
SWING AND MISS, WE HAVEN‘T BEEN
ACCUSTOMED TO SEEING DJ SWING
AND MISS AS MUCH BUT YESTERDAY
WITH THE HANGING BREAKING BALL,
HE WENT DEEP.
KARL: STAYED ALIVE ON A LATE
EMERGENCY HACK AT 91.
HAD GREAT SUCCESS AGAINST THE
METS IN HIS CAREER COME OVER
.300.
THE HOME RUN LAST NIGHT WAS HIS
FIRST IN 12 GAMES.
DAVID: LEMAHIEU HAS ALWAYS BEEN
DISCIPLINED.
HITS THE FASTBALL THE OTHER WAY
AND PULLS OFF-SPEED PITCHES.
KARL: DONALDSON AT SECOND.
RIZZO AT FIRST.
BRIGHAM ON AND RELIEF OF
VERLANDER IN A 1-1 GAME.
NOBODY ELSE, TWO ON.
STRIKE THREE.
LEMAHIEU IS GONE.
BIG STRIKEOUT FOR BRIGHAM.
DAVID: BE IN PINK.
-- PRETTY IN PINK.
A LITTLE RUG BURN ON THE INSIDE
CORNER.
EDUARDO: PERFECTLY FRAMED.
DAVID: PERFECTLY FLOPPED?
KARL: KINER-FALEFA WILL NOT
SWING AT THE FIRST ONE.
OUTSIDE, 1-0.
TRYING TO AVOID THE THREE
STRIKEOUT NIGHT, KINER-FALEFA.
INFIELD SQUEEZED UP THE MIDDLE.
THAT IS A STRIKE.
IMPLIED AS A SHORTSTOP THAT HE
HAD A DIFFERENT APPROACH THAN HE
DOES AS A CENTER FIELDER.
IS IT A DIFFERENT WAY OF
THINKING?
DAVID: HEADING IN STRUCTURES --
INSTRUCTORS -- HITTING
INSTRUCTORS HAVE WORKED WITH
HIM.
THEY THOUGHT THERE WAS MORE FOR
FELT LIKE HE WAS PREOCCUPIED
WITH PLAYING DEFENSE AT SHORT
AND STRUGGLED AT THE END OF THE
YEAR.
THIS YEAR, DIFFERENT MINDSET.
YOU ARE STRONG.
YOU HAVE MORE TO GIVE.
LOAD UP.
LET IT GO.
KARL: HAS THREE HOMERS IN HIS
LAST 13 GAMES.
FOUR ALL OF LAST YEAR.
THERE ARE THE THREE HOMERS.
DAVID: HE HAD A CHANCE TO BE ONE
OF THE MOST VALUABLE SUPER
UTILITY GUYS.
HE CAN CATCH AS WELL.
KARL: BRIGHAM LOOKING FOR A
GROUND BALL.
THERE IT IS.
LINDOR.
MCNEIL.
THAT ONE GETS AWAY FROM VIENTOS
AND THAT WILL ALLOW THE GO-AHEAD
RUN TO SCORE.
VIENTOS HAS BEEN GREAT ALL NIGHT
AT SCOOPING BALLS AND THIS ONE
GOT BY HIM AND ALLOWED THE RUN
TO SCORE FROM THIRD.
EDUARDO: THAT IS ONE THAT YOU
HAVE TO KNOW THE RUNNER COME UP
WITH IN YOUR BACK POCKET.
INSTEAD HE THROWS IT.
LOOK AT HIS LEFT FOOT.
BY THE TIME IT GETS TO WHERE HE
IS TRYING TO GET TO, TO SPREAD
APART WITH HIS LEGS, HARD TO GET
TO THE BALL FROM WHERE HE IS AT.
MOVING TOWARDS HIS RIGHT AND IT
GETS PAST HIM.
NO NEED TO BE THAT SPREAD APART
AT FIRST BASE.
AS GOOD OF DEFENSE AS HE PLAYED
EARLY ON, THIS COST THEM A RUN.
KARL: FIELDER‘S CHOICE, 6-4 E4.
THE GAME IS NOT TIED ANY LONGER.
EDUARDO: MARK VIENTOS HAS HAD A
NICE NIGHT.
SAW THAT ONE EARLY ON BUT THIS
ONE BY LINDOR AS WELL, SAVES HIM
FROM AN ERROR.
THIS ONE, DIVES A LITTLE BIT.
YOU WONDER IF HE SHOULD HAVE BUT
THIS ONE, THE LEGS TOO SPREAD
APART.
IT IS A PLAY BE AVERAGE FIRST
BASEMAN USUALLY MAKES.
KARL: MCKINNEY AGAINST BROOKS
RALEY.
SWINGS AT THE FIRST ONE.
THE ERROR FROM MCNEIL GIVES THE
YANKEES A 2-1 LEAD.
LONG HALF INNING FOR COLE
TOURIST UNDER THE ASSUMPTION HE
IS COMING BACK.
THE NUMBERS ON THE LEFTY RALEY.
ACTIVATED OFF THE IL IN THE
MIDDLE OF MAY.
ONE RUN IN 13 GAMES.
DONALDSON WAS WALKED, RIZZO GOT
HIT BY A PITCH AND THE WALK
COMES BACK AND SCORES THE RUN
AGAINST THE METS.
YANKEES SCORED THE RUN WITHOUT A
HIT.
1-1, RUNNER GOES.
GOOD JUMP.
THE THROW IS OFF.
KINER-FALEFA IS IN THERE AT
THIRD AND PICKS UP HIS SEVENTH
STOLEN BASE.
OF THE SEASON.
KINER-FALEFA GOT A TERRIFIC JUMP
.
EDUARDO: ON A LOT OF FOOTWORK
THERE BY ALVAREZ BEHIND THE
PLATE.
NO CHANCE FOR LINDOR AT ALL TO
GET KINER-FALEFA.
KARL: HALFWAY DOWN THE
THIRD-BASE LINE.
HERE HE COMES.
ISAIAH KINER-FALEFA READ AROUND
THE BASES AND THE YANKEES HAVE A
3-1 LEAD.
BROOKS RALEY NEVER GAVE HIM A
LOOK.
EDUARDO: RIGHT DOWN THE LINE,
THROWING FROM THE WINDUP, HAD
THE LEFTY, VERY DELIBERATE.
AS SOON I SEE STARTS HIS MOTION,
HE IS GONE.
KARL: TWO RUNS WITHOUT A HIT.
COMMUNICATION BREAKDOWN AS THE
BALL SAT BETWEEN LINDOR AND
ESCOBAR.
MCKINNEY IS A BORN-AGAIN --
ABOARD AGAIN.
HOW COME NO ONE IS HELPING RALEY
OUT THERE?
DAVID: A WHOLE LOT OF NOTHING
GOING ON OUT THERE EXCEPT FOR
KINER-FALEFA, HALFWAY DOWN THE
LINE.
NO ONE NOTICES.
WATCH THIS.
ESCOBAR AT THIRD.
WHOLE LOT OF NOTHING.
EDUARDO: AND WITH TWO OUTS AS
WELL.
IS IT THIS YEAR KINER-FALEFA IS
PLAYING WITH MORE CONFIDENCE?
DAVID: FREEDOM.
KARL: I‘M SHOCKED NO ONE WAS
YELLING TO BROOKS RALEY.
PERHAPS AT THE END OF THE THE
GAME, IN A POST GAME WE WILL BE
HERE DURING THEY WERE, BUT THERE
WASN‘T MOVEMENT FROM ANYBODY BUT
KINER-FALEFA WHO STOLE SECOND,
CAME TO THIRD, COMES IN AND
SCORES BY STEALING HOME.
MATT‘S RELIEVERS HAVE LEFT THEM
DOWN.
A WALK AND A HIT BETTER.
RALEY IS BEHIND 3-1 TO TREVINO
AFTER GIVING UP A HIT TO
MCKINNEY.
DAVID: HAVE YOU EVER HAD A CALL
OF A STOLEN HOME PLATE?
KARL: AT THE MAJOR LEAGUE LEVEL?
DAVID: FROM THE WINDUP.
RALEY IS LEFT-HANDED.
HIS BACK TO THE RUNNER.
HE COULD ALMOST SEE HIM.
KARL: POPPED UP.
MCNEIL SAYS HE HAS IT.
AN AGGRESSIVE INNING FOR THE
YANKEES.
A MESSY HALF FOR THE NEW YORK
METS.
HERE HE COMES AND THERE HE GOES.
STEALING HOME BY ISAIAH
KINER-FALEFA.
THE YANKEES TRYING TO TAKE THEM
BOTH IN THE SUBWAY SERIES.
KARL: IKF THE FIRST YANKEE TO
STEAL HOME SINCE DIDI GREGORIUS
IN 2016.
THE NEW YORK METS MADE A MESS OF
THAT INNING AND WASTED A GOOD
VERLANDER START, NOW TRAILING
3-1.
JIMMY CORDERO IS ON THE MOUND
AND HERE COMES SOME GAS.
THE FIRST ONE IS 97 MPH.
HIGH STRIKEOUT RATE, ONLY WALKED
EIGHT OF 105.
THAT HE HAS SEEN.
GOOD PITCH AT 97.
A LITTLE PAUSE FROM BILL MILLER.
HOW ABOUT THE CATCHER?
A LOT OF TIMES YOU WILL SEE THE
BASERUNNER AT THIRD TRY TO
DISTRACT THE PITCHER.
BUT HE WAS SO FAR DOWN THE LINE.
ESCOBAR WAS STANDING AT THIRD.
THE METS DUGOUT DIDN‘T APPEAR TO
BE YELLING, ALVAREZ DID SEE HIM,
FIRST BASEMAN DID NOT ALERT THE
PITCHER TO WHICH.
YOU BROUGHT UP AN INTERESTING
POINT.
RALEY ROLLED THE HITTER COME THE
BALL IS DEAD AND THE RUNNER GOES
BACK.
DAVID: LOOKED LIKE THAT S WAWHAT
HE WAS TRYING TO DO.
KARL: THE FIELD HAS GROWN QUIET
AFTER THAT.
HOW ABOUT WHAT KINER-FALEFA HAS
DONE?
THEY BROUGHT IN THE YOUNGSTER
FULL DAY AT SHORTSTOP.
KINER-FALEFA DIDN‘T HAVE A
POSITION BUT HAS ESTABLISHED
HIMSELF AS A VALUABLE MEMBER OF
THE TEAM.
HARRISON BADER IS YOUR EVERYDAY
CENTER ELDER WHEN JUDGE IS IN
RIGHT BUT THERE HAS TO BE A
POSITION FOR THAT GUY.
DAVID: NEVER PLAYED THE OUTFIELD
BEFORE AND NOW HE IS PLAYING
CENTER FIELD.
KARL: 3-2 TO ALVAREZ.
FILED OFF -- FOULED OFF OF
MILLER, THE UMPIRE.
AND A LITTLE BLOOPER, SHALLOW
LEFT FIELD.
THAT WILL GET DOWN.
ALVAREZ, 74 MPH OFF THE BAT BUT
THAT IS A LEADOFF SINGLE.
EDUARDO: BEST TIME TO DO IT WITH
TWO OUTS.
TAKES OFF IMMEDIATELY.
A LOOK AT STATCAST NUMBERS.
SPRINT SPEED.
TOPPING OFF AROUND 25.5 PER
MINUTE.
DAVID: ONLY HAD TO RUN 45 FEET
FROM THAT POINT.
EDUARDO: PRETTY COOL GRAPHIC
THERE.
KARL: ANOTHER ONE TO LEFT.
THIS IS PLAYABLE FOR MCKINNEY.
ONE DOWN AS BATY FLIES OUT.
2023 MLB ALL-STAR BALLOTS ARE
OPEN.
SCAN THE QR CODE OR VISIT
MLB.COM/VOTE TO DECIDE WHO
REPRESENTS YOUR FAVORITE TEAM
THIS SUMMER.
THAT IS THE 2023 ALL-STAR BALLOT
NOW OPEN, QR CODE ON THE SCREEN.
FEELS LIKE A LONG TIME AGO WHEN
FANS HAND DELIVERED VOTES.
THE METS ARE IN BUSINESS HERE IN
THE BOTTOM OF THE SEVENTH.
TWO ON AGAINST CORDERO.
PHAM HAS TWO HITS.
EDUARDO: 99 MPH SINKER, HIT IT,
95 OFF THE BAT.
INNER PART OF THE PLATE, BRING
THE HANDS IN.
TOMMY LIKES IT.
DAVID: HE CAN HIT A FASTBALL.
KARL: NEITHER OF YOU ARE
SURPRISED COLE‘S NIGHT ENDED.
WAS HE DONE WITH THE NUMBER OF
PITCHES?
DAVID: EXPENDED HIMSELF THE LAST
COUPLE INNINGS AND HAD CRAMPING
ISSUES A COUPLE STARTS AGO.
KARL: ESCOBAR UP THE MIDDLE.
VOLPE, TAG, NO DOUBLE PLAY.
SLAPPED THE TAG ON PHAM BUT THEY
DIDN‘T HAVE A FLIP THROW TO GET
A DOUBLE PLAY.
NOW IT IS FIRST AND THIRD.
DAVID: HITS YOU SOFTLY.
YOU HAVE TO COME AND GET IT.
YOU CAN‘T WAIT FOR THE BALL.
AT THAT POINT, HE TRIES TO WHEEL
AND LOOK AT THIRD.
KARL: A LOT OF TALK ABOUT
VIENTOS -- ABOUT VOLPE AND THE
IDEA THAT HE HAS BEEN IN A
HITTING SLUMP AND YOU THINK
ABOUT SETTING HIM DOWN.
THE DEDICATION TO VOLPE BEING ON
THE MAJOR LEAGUE TEAM, THEY SAY
HE IS ROCK SOLID AND HE HAS
CERTAINLY EARNED THAT ESPECIALLY
GIVEN HIS ABILITY TO MAKE
ADJUSTMENTS AS HE WAS COMING UP
FROM THE MINORS.
SEEMS TO START SLOW AND FIGURE
IT OUT.
MAYBE HE IS DOING THAT AGAIN.
UPDATE FROM KEVIN CONNORS, TWO
DOWN, RUNNERS AT FIRST AND
THIRD.
VIENTOS.
ALSO CAN HIT A FASTBALL.
THE GO-AHEAD RUN.
1-0.
SHOWALTER TALKED ABOUT THE
YANKEE BULLPEN.
HE THINKS GIVEN THE ARMS THEY
HAVE, IT IS AS GOOD OF A BULLPEN
AS THERE IS IN THE BIG LEAGUES.
THE NUMBER OF GUYS THAT CAN
THROW 100 WITH MOVEMENT, HE SAYS
IT IS AS GOOD AS ANY IN
BASEBALL.
THE NUMBERS BACK IT UP.
CORDERO FINDS HIMSELF IN A 3-0
TO WHOLE.
BRANDON NIMMO ON DECK.
OUR NACCHIO WARMING UP.
-- MARINACCIO WARMING UP.
DAVID: AARON BOONE SAID HE WOULD
HAVE TO GET CREATIVE TO GET THE
FINAL OUTS.
KARL: TAKING IT ALL THE WAY.
3-1.
DAVID: IT‘S NOT JUST ABOUT
WHETHER YOU PITCHED LAST NIGHT.
IT IS THE THREE OUT OF FOUR,
CONSECUTIVE GAMES THAT ADD UP.
KARL: BALL FOUR TO VIENTOS AND
CORDERO HAS WALKED THE BASES
LOADED IN THE SEVENTH.
HERE COMES AARON BOONE, AND WE
WILL HAVE MARINACCIO.
HE MAKES THE SIGN TO BRING IN
THE WRITING.
HERE WE GO.
TWO OUTS, BASES LOADED, DOWN
TWO, BOTTOM OF THE SEVENTH AND
THE METS HAVE THE LEADOFF HITTER
COMING UP.
KARL: THIS WAS THE CLAY HOLMES
SITUATION LAST NIGHT.
TONIGHT IT IS MARINACCIO WITH
THE BASES LOADED.
HE WILL FACE NIMMO.
ALVAREZ AT THIRD, ESCOBAR AT
SECOND.
-MARINACCIO‘S FIRST ONE JUST
MISSES AT 93.
BALL ONE.
YANKEES THREE, METS ONE.
NIMMO FOULS IT BACK.
DAVID: MARINACCIO AND NIMMO AND
THIS MATCHUP, A REALLY GOOD
CHANGEUP FOR MARINACCIO HERE.
KARL: LAST FOUR SEAM FASTBALL AT
92.
HE HIT HIM.
HE WILL BE CALLED BACK OR IS HE
POINTING HIM TO FIRST?
POINTING HIM TO FIRST.
THAT WILL BRING IN A RUN.
FOR A SECOND MILLER HAD NIMMO‘S
ATTENTION LIKE DID YOU SAY I
DIDN‘T GET OUT OF THE WAY?
BUT A RUN COMES IN AND IT IS A
ONE RUN GAME.
EDUARDO: BRANDON NIMMO, AND THE
BACK OF HIS MIND HE IS THINKING
I‘M GOING TO WIND UP IN THE SAME
PLACE AS YESTERDAY.
THIS TIME HE DRIVES ONE IN.
KARL: MARTE STRUCK OUT WITH THE
BASES LOADED YESTERDAY BUT
MARINACCIO, FOUR-SEAM FASTBALL
AT 91.
EDUARDO: MARINACCIO THREW 21
PITCHES YESTERDAY.
KARL: YOU KNOW YOUR BULLPEN IS
TAXED.
COLE COMES OUT OF THE GAME AND
MARINACCIO HAS NEARLY HIT MARTE.
IT IS 3-0.
EDUARDO: TAKE TWO OR TAKE 3.
KARL: THERE IS A STRIKE.
ESCOBAR AT THIRD.
VIENTOS AT SECOND.
NIMMO AT FIRST.
MARTE GOOD HITTER‘S COUNT, 3-1.
RIPS THAT ONE INTO LEFT FIELD.
HERE COMES ESCOBAR AND THAT WILL
BE IT.
THEY HAVE A CHANCE TO THROW
BEHIND NIMMO.
THEY DO.
BRANDON NIMMO WAS TOO FAR OFF.
HE THOUGHT VIENTOS WOULD BE
WAIVED IN AND THE SWIM MOVE
DIDN‘T WORK.
BUCK SHOWALTER HAS HIS HAND UP.
HE IS WAITING TO HEAR FROM THE
REPLAY OFFICIAL.
THEY ARE GOING TO APPEAL IT.
DID THE LEFT-HAND GET IN BEFORE
THE TAG?
THE NEW YORK METS ARE
CHALLENGING THE OUT CALL AT
SECOND BASE.
EDUARDO: THAT IS CLOSE.
BECAUSE HE WAS CALLED OUT, IT
COULD STAND BUT KEEP AN EYE ON
THIS ONE.
I THINK HE IS SAFE.
DAVID: THE GLOVE HITS THE CHIN
RIGHT HERE.
THIS IS A GOOD SHOT.
I DON‘T KNOW IF THAT IS ENOUGH
TO OVERTURN.
IT‘S REALLY CLOSE.
KARL: IN NEW YORK THEY ARE
LOOKING AT IT CLOSELY.
THEY PROBABLY HAVE A YOU MORE
ANGLES -- A FEW MORE ANGLES.
THIS IS A HUGE, HUGE CALL.
NIMMO DIDN‘T LOOK UP AT VIENTOS
WHO WAS HELD THAT THIRD ON THE
SHOT FROM MARTE.
EDUARDO: THAT MAN RIGHT THERE IS
HOPING FOR THAT TO BE REVERSED.
WHEN YOU ARE RUNNING FROM FIRST
TO THIRD YOU HAD BETTER KEEP
YOUR HEAD UP IF YOU HAVE A LEAD
RUNNER AND HE DIDN‘T.
JOEY CORA CLEARLY HOLDING THE
RUNNER AT THIRD.
DAVID: THAT WAS A GOOD SHOT
RIGHT THERE.
AFTER REVIEW,HE CALL ON THE
FIELD STANDS.
THE RUNNER IS OUT.
THE METS WILL LOSE THEIR
CHALLENGE.
KARL: WOW.
INSTANT REPLAY.
NIMMO OUT.
GAME TIED.
KARL: BRANDON NIMMO ROUNDED
SECOND AS IF THERE WAS NO
QUESTION IN HIS MIND THAT
VIENTOS WAS SCORING.
CORA PUT THE BRAKES ON VIENTOS
AND THAT COST THE METS.
WE ARE TIED.
OTHERWISE THEY WOULD HAVE HAD
THE BASES LOADED.
WITH MCNEIL COMING UP.
LUCKY COUPLE NIGHTS WITH NIMMO
AND THE OUTFIELD AND THE
BASERUNNING MISTAKE.
EDUARDO: AS GOOD AS BRANDON
NIMMO HAS BEEN IN THE BATTER‘S
BOX, IN THE OUTFIELD, THAT HAS
ALWAYS BEEN HIS ACHILLES HEEL,
BASERUNNING.
KARL: ADAM OTTAVINO THE NEXT
PITCHER FOR THE METS AS WE START
THE EIGHTH.
GETS A STRIKE.
GREAT CONVERSATION WITH ADAM
OTTAVINO ABOUT HOW HE IS
PITCHING DIFFERENTLY THAN WHAT
WE WERE ACCUSTOMED TO.
DAVID: THE MASTER OF TECHNOLOGY.
HAS HIS OWN SHOP IN HARLEM THAT
OTHER LAWYERS GO TO.
KARL: 1-2.
FAIR BALL.
HE TAKES OFF FOR SECOND BASE.
MARTE FIXED IT UP.
VOLPE DELIVERS A DOUBLE TO LEAD
THE EIGHTH.
EDUARDO: TWO STRIKES AGAIN FOR
VOLPE TAKING THE BALL THE OTHER
WAY.
THE OTHER TIME WAS MOVING
TREVINO TO THIRD.
THIS TIME, THE BALL GOT TOO MUCH
OF THE PLATE ON THE 1-2 COUNT.
ON THE OFF DAY, THAT HAS BEEN
PAYING DIVIDENDS YESTERDAY AND
TODAY IN THE SUBWAY SERIES.
DAVID: THESE TEAMS PUNCHING BACK
AND FORTH, ANSWERING.
KARL: JAKE BAUERS HAS A SINGLE
AND AN R.B.I. AND TWO FLY OUTS.
YOU COULD MAKE THE CASE HE HAS
HAD AS GOOD OF A BAT AS ANY
YANKEE TONIGHT.
STRAIGHT FASTBALL, FOUR SEAMER.
TALK ABOUT SWEEPERS AND SLIDERS.
OTTAVINO MADE A LIVING, NOW HE
HAS GONE BACK TO MORE OF A
SINKER BUT HE USES THE
TECHNOLOGY.
HE SAYS YOU HAVE TO READ THE
BATTERERS.
-- THE BATTERS.
DAVID: ADDITIONALLY HE TALKED
ABOUT HISTORICALLY SPEAKING, HE
WAS ENCOURAGED TO THROW
TWO-SEAMERS TO LEFTIES.
THOSE WILL FLATTEN OUT AND GET
HARD.
FOUR-SEAMERS TO LEFTIES AND
TWO-SEAMERS TO RIGHTIES.
THAT HAS CHANGED OVER THE PAST
20 YEARS.
KARL: VERLANDER AND COLE WERE
OUTSTANDING.
THIS GAME WAS 00 -- 0-0 INTO THE
BOTTOM OF THE FIFTH.
THE METS BROKE THROUGH AND
EVERYTHING CHANGED ONCE THE
BULLPENS WERE ACTIVATED.
BOTH MANAGERS ACKNOWLEDGED, MY
BULLPEN IS TIRED.
DAVID: YOU WONDER IF BAUERS IS
DOING THAT ON HIS OWN.
2-1 PITCH, SWINGING AROUND.
EDUARDO: I BELIEVE HE WAS.
KARL: WICKED PITCH.
THAT IS WHAT OTTAVINO IS KNOWN
FOR, THE CUTTER IN HARD FOR THE
LEFTY.
DAVID: YOU CAN SEE VOLPE DANCING
AROUND OUT THERE.
THAT IS ONE OF OTTAVINO‘S
WEAKNESS, SLOW DELIVERY TO HOME
PLATE CAN BE TAKEN ADVANTAGE OF.
KARL: WHAT HE DOES AT SECOND, WE
WILL SEE HOW FAR HE DANCES OFF.
HE IS DOING IT AGAIN.
OTTAVINO STRIKES HIM OUT.
FILTHY CUTTER TO GET BAUERS.
LET‘S GO BACK TO THE PLATE THAT
ENDED THE SEVENTH -- THE PLAY
THAT ENDED THE SEVENTH.
HERE COMES NIMMO INTO THE SHOT.
EDUARDO: THAT IS ONE THAT I‘M OF
THE CALL COULD HAVE GONE EITHER
WAY.
IT WENT THE WAY MANY THOUGHT IT
WASN‘T GOING TO GO.
AS A BASE RUNNER, KNOWING YOU
ARE A TRAILER, YOU HAVE TO SEE
AHEAD AND MAKE SURE VIENTOS WAS
GOING HOME FOR YOU TO GO.
DAVID: HAD HIS HEAD DOWN THE
HALLWAY.
EDUARDO: JOEY CORA IS GOING TO
HAVE CONVERSATIONS WITH BOTH
VIENTOS ON THE DEFENSIVE SIDE,
AND BRANDON NIMMO ON THE
BASERUNNING.
KARL: FIRST BASE OPEN.
HERE IS STANTON.
PITCHED CAREFULLY HERE.
4-11, TWO HOMERS, FOUR K‘S.
EDUARDO: IF I‘M A HITTER,
STANTON AT THE PLATE, I WANT THE
RUNNER AT SECOND TO STAY STILL.
BE READY IN SCORING POSITION.
KARL: I HEARD HIM SAY SOMETHING
ABOUT A VIOLATION.
DID THEY CALL MCNEIL FOR BEING
ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE BAG?
YES.
DAVID: THAT IS WHAT THEY ARE
CALLING.
HE IS PLAYING LIKE A FIRST
BASEMAN, STRADDLED THE BAG.
KARL: HERE COMES SHOWALTER.
DAVID: THE SHIFT RULES.
EDUARDO: THIS IS INTERESTING.
IF I‘M NOT MISTAKEN MCNEIL -- OH
NO. WATCH HIS FOOT.
IT WAS ON THE SHORTSTOP SIDE OF
THE BAG.
HE IS RIGHT.
VERY GOOD CALL.
KARL: SPLIT SECOND BASE IN HALF
AS HIS RIGHT FOOT WAS ON THE
OTHER SIDE.
WASN‘T ON THE DIRT ON THE OTHER
SIDE BUT IT WAS ON THE RIGHT
SIDE OF THE BAG.
EDUARDO: AS SOON AS THE FOOT IS
ON THAT SIDE OF THE BAG --
DAVID: LOOKS LIKE IT DOES ON THE
DIRT FROM THIS ANGLE.
-- IT DIAZ ON THE DIRT FROM THIS
ANGLE.
KARL: BILL MILLER FROM HOME
PLATE SEEING IT.
EDUARDO: HE IS TRYING TO SAY
THAT IS WHERE HE WAS AND THAT‘S
NOT WHERE HE WAS ORIGINALLY.
DAVID: NOT THE SPIRIT OF THE
RULE EITHER.
KARL: ONE BALL, ONE STRIKE.
DAVID: THE SPIRIT OF THE RULE
CHANGE WAS TO PREVENT MAJOR
SHIFTING, NOT-SO-SUBTLE PUT ON
THE WRONG SIDE OF THE BAT.
TECHNICALLY THE RIGHT CALL BUT
NOT IN THE SPIRIT OF THE RULE.
KARL: 1-1 TO STANTON.
2-1.
EDUARDO: FROM THE DUGOUT‘S, AND
WE HAVE HEARD PLAYERS CHIRPING
SAYING DON‘T FORGET ABOUT THE
HITTERS.
YOU CAN‘T FORGET ABOUT NUMBER
27, GIANCARLO STANTON.
HE WANTS TO DANCE AROUND HIM
STEAL THIRD.
YOU HAVE TO EXECUTE YOUR PITCHES
WITH STANTON AT THE PLATE.
KARL: 24 CAREER HOMERS AT CITI
FIELD AND DIDN‘T LOOK GOOD ON
THAT ONE.
NO VIOLATION AGAINST MCNEIL.
STRIKE THREE.
DAVID: CHANGEUP DOWN AND IN FOR
OTTAVINO.
HE TALKED ABOUT SWITCHING UP HIS
BATTERERS.
WE HAVE NEVER SEEN HIM DO THAT
BEFORE.
KARL: TWO BALLS, TWO STRIKES.
VOLPE NEARLY WENT.
STANTON HIGH CHOPPER.
LINDOR BACKS UP.
LOOKED LIKE VOLPE WOULD NEARLY
GO ON HIS OWN.
SECOND OUT.
NOW IT IS UP TO JOSH DONALDSON
IN THE EIGHTH INNING OF A TIE
BALLGAME.
VOLPE WILL COME DOWN THE
THIRD-BASE LINE.
DONALDSON POPS IT UP.
PHAM IS UNDER IT.
OTTAVINO GETS OUT OF IT.
A LOT OF ACTION AFTER THE
LEADOFF DOUBLE BUT STRANDED UP
THIRD.
MCNEIL, LINDOR AND ALVAREZ AFTER
THIS.
EDUARDO:
EDUARDO:ED OR --
WIOUTHT THE EXPRESS WRITTEN
CONSENT.
KARL: MLB LIVE HAD A HUGE
PRESENCE OF THE GOVERNORS BALL
MUSIC FESTIVAL IN QUEENS.
THE INTERACTIVE SPACE, A CHANCE
TO LISTEN TO MUSIC AND CHECK OUT
OUR WORK.
BRING IN CLASSIC RIVALRIES TO
LIFE.
THE GOVERNORS BALL IS WIDELY
POPULAR.
3-3 GAME, TOMMY KAHNLE ON.
HE HAS WORKED HIS WAY BACK INTO
THIS BULLPEN AND HAS YET TO
ALLOW AN EARNED RUN.
HE WILL GET JEFF MCNEIL, LINDOR
AND ALVAREZ.
THE FIRST PITCH MISSES.
EDUARDO: SCOUTING REPORT IS
SIMPLE ON HIM.
BE AWARE OF THE CHANGEUPS.
HAS GOOD LIFE ON IT.
ALSO THROWS IN THE MID-90‘S.
THE CHANGEUP.
KARL: MCNEIL POPPED UP ON THE
INFIELD.
HERE COMES RIZZO.
EASY ONE.
JEFF MCNEIL GOT TOGETHER WITH
HIS MANAGER BUCK SHOWALTER WAS
EXPLAINING TO HIM WHY HE DIDN‘T
THINK THERE WAS A VIOLATION ON A
BALL STANTON SWUNG AT AND THEY
CALLED A NO PITCH.
IT WAS INTERESTING CHAD WHITSON
WAS STANDING RIGHT BEHIND MCNEIL
BUT IT WAS THE HOME PLATE UMPIRE
WHOSE VOICE YOU CAN HEAR SAYING
THAT‘S A VIOLATION.
KAHNLE FIRES IN THE FASTBALL TO
LINDOR.
THE WAY THE NUMBERS BEAR OUTCOME
OF THE ADVANTAGE TILTS TOWARDS
THE YANKEES WHEN IT COMES TO
BULLPEN GAMES.
THAT WAS WAY OFF.
CALLED A STRIKE ON A CHANGEUP TO
LINDOR.
EDUARDO: FRANCISCO IS ON HIS WAY
TO SECOND.
LET ME ASSESS THE ZONE RIGHT
NOW.
YOU HAVE TO OPEN UP A LOT MORE.
YOU HAVE TO GIVE UP THE INSIDE
PART OF THE PLATE NOW.
DAVID: TREMENDOUS MOVEMENT ON
THAT PITCH.
SOMETIMES UMPIRES GET FOOLED AS
WELL.
KARL: GOT HIM.
LINDOR GONE, 89 MPH CHANGEUP.
KARL: THE PARTY JUST KEEPS
GOING.
EDUARDO: ALL THE TIME NOW.
OUR CASA IS YOUR CASA.
DAVID: SUNDAY NIGHT AND
WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
KARL: IF IT ENDS IN A Y.
THAT IS IN, 2-0 TO ALVAREZ.
HOME RUNS ON THE SEASON, DAVID
ROBERTSON WARMING AND THE NEW
YORK METS BULLPEN.
TWO BALLS, NO STRIKES.
ALL SORTS OF POWER IN THAT BAT
AND THAT BODY.
HE WAS SWINGING FOR THE BRIDGE.
DAVID: YOU CAN SEE WHY HE WAS
THE TOP RANKED PROSPECT.
TREMENDOUS LEVERAGE AND SPEED.
KARL: A GOOD ONE THERE, 90
MILE-PER-HOUR CHANGEUP.
BACK IN THE COUNT IS KAHNLE AT
2-2.
EDUARDO: LEFT THAT ONE UP.
GOT AWAY WITH IT.
NOT AFRAID TO THROW THE CHANGEUP
TO LEFTIES AND TO RIGHTIES.
KARL: RIGHT BICEPS TENDINITIS,
MISSED THE FIRST 56 GAMES OF THE
SEASON DID KAHNLE.
MISSED INSIDE.
3-2.
DAVID: DEFINITELY IN THE
CATEGORY OF A POWER CHANGEUP,
LOW 90‘S, UPPER 80‘S.
KARL: FELT LIKE OLD-SCHOOL
BASEBALL THE LAST COUPLE NIGHTS
AT CITI FIELD.
EVEN WITH THE PITCH CLOCK.
THERE IS NUANCE TO THE GAME, AS
WE SAW WITH MCNEIL AT SECOND
BASE.
3-2.
THAT IS FOUL.
DAVID: THEY HAVE TO GO BACK AND
FORTH FOR THESE TWO GAMES.
YANKEES WITH A BIG COMEBACK LAST
NIGHT, THE METS COMING BACK IN
THIS GAME AS WELL.
NICE COMEBACK LAST INNING,
OTHERWISE MARRED BY THE NIMMO
BASERUNNING.
KARL: THAT ALMOST, THE BALL
WINDS UP IN THE GLOVE OF TREVINO
.
BACK TO BACK PUNCH OUTS LINDOR
AND ALVAREZ.
RIZZO, LEMAHIEU,
KARL: LISTEN TO EVERY MLB GAME
LIVE OR ON-DEMAND, ON-DEMAND, MI
BASEBALL, AND LIVE LOOK IN‘S ON
MLB BIG INNING.
NO BLACKOUTS.
VISIT MLB.COM/AT-BAT FOR
DETAILS.
PART OF THE FIFTH LARGEST
REGULAR-SEASON CROWD IN CITI
FIELD HISTORY TONIGHT.
DAVID ROBERTSON, ONE OF THOSE
GUYS WHO HAS PITCHED FOR BOTH
THE YANKEES AND METS, ON TO FACE
ANTHONY RIZZO, DJ LEMAHIEU, AND
ISIAH KINER-FALEFA.
3-3, NINTH INNING.
RIZZO.
HE CANNOT FOR THE LIFE OF ME HIT
ANTHONY RIZZO.
EDUARDO: RIGHT IN FRONT OF THE
PLATE.
THEY ARE GIVING FRANCISCO
ALVAREZ A BREATHER HERE.
HIT HIM WITH THE TOP PART OF THE
CHEST PROTECTOR.
KARL: WE HAVE SEEN THAT ALREADY
WITH RIZZO TONIGHT, HE GOT HIT
BY THAT PITCH IN THE SEVENTH
INNING.
BUT ALL CLEAR.
84 MILE AN HOUR KNUCKLE CURVE
FROM DAVID ROBERTSON, WHO TALKED
WITH US EARLIER IN THE
CLUBHOUSE.
THE OUTFIELD IS SO GOOD, HE IS
JUST READY TO GO AND GO.
DAVID: HIS PITCH STUFF LOOKS AS
GOOD AS IT EVER HAS, 94 MILES AN
HOUR WITH THE FOUR-SEAM CUTTER.
KARL: CURVEBALL TO RIZZO AND GOT
HIM THERE.
SEVENTH INNING, HUGE INNING
HERE.
ISIAH KINER-FALEFA.
A STEAL OF HOME.
TIED THE GAME UP AND NIMMO DID
NOT PUT THE BRAKES ON.
HE BANGS RIGHT INTO IT, THROWN
OUT TRYING TO GET BACK TO
SECOND.
THAT ENDED THE INNING, OTHERWISE
BASES WOULD HAVE BEEN LOADED.
LEMAHIEU SWINGS AND MISSES FROM
ROBERTSON.
DAVID: GOOD BASE RUNNING VERSUS
BAD BASERUNNING AND MENTAL
MISTAKES.
KARL: 94 MILES AN HOUR OR A
STRIKE.
ROBERTSON FOLLOWED RIVERA AND
THEY ALMOST MIRRORED EACH OTHER,
LIKE ROBERTSON WAS RIVERA LIGHT.
THAT BECAME SUCH A WEAPON.
THAT‘S A FAIR BALL, OFF THE TARP
, AND GOING TO ALLOW THEM A FEW
TO GET INTO SECOND EASILY.
FAN DID NOT KNOW IF IT WAS GOING
TO HIT ALL THE WAY DOWN INTO THE
CORNER.
INSTEAD IT HIT OFF THE TARP.
DJ LEMAHIEU STARTING TO WARM UP,
LAST COUPLE OF NIGHTS A HOMER
AND TONIGHT A DOUBLE.
EDUARDO: KEEPS THIS ONE FAIR
TOO, COMING UP FOR HIS FOURTH
AT-BAT, 0-3, SALVAGING THE NIGHT
WITH A DOUBLE RIGHT OFF THE
LINE.
DAVID: BREAKING BALL STAYED ON
THE INNER PART OF THE PLATE,
ALLOWING DJ TO DROP THE BARREL.
KARL: DJ LEMAHIEU WITH THAT
DOUBLE ON THE GAME.
PINCH RUNNER IS IN AT SECOND.
NOW WE WILL HAVE A MEETING ON
THE MOUND.
GLEYBER HAS GOT A BAD.
CABRERA IS THE GUY AT SECOND
BASE AND WILL BE RUNNING AGAINST
ROBERTSON.
TORRES WILL HIT FOR
KINER-FALEFA.
WHEELS ARE SPINNING, FIRST BASE
IS OPEN.
MCKINNEY ON DECK.
FOURTH DOUBLE OF THE GAME FOR
THE.
GOOD JOB THERE, A GUY WHO HAS
REALLY IMPROVED HIS BLOCKING,
ALVAREZ.
ONE OUT, KEEPING THAT RUNNER OFF
THIRD BASE.
DAVID: ALVAREZ, MUCH MORE
ATHLETIC THAN I THOUGHT.
HE RUNS FAIRLY WELL.
YOU KNOW ABOUT HIS POWER.
KARL: GLEYBER MUST 52, 11
HOMERS, 28 R.B.I.
BIG SWING AND A MISS, SLIDER
THAT WAS UP.
EDUARDO: DON‘T THROW THAT SAME
PITCH TO HIM THOUGH.
KARL: MCNEIL ON THE RIGHT SIDE
OF THE BAG KEEPS AN EYE ON
CABRERA.
THAT BREAKING PITCH NEARLY HIT
GLEYBER TORRES.
MCKINNEY HAS GOT TWO HITS, A
DOUBLE AND A SINGLE.
HE IS NEXT UP.
LABOR TORRES PINCH-HITTING,
TRYING TO GIVE HIM THE LEAD.
DID NOT GET THE CALL.
THAT HAS BEEN A STRIKE CERTAINLY
ON MANY OCCASIONS TONIGHT.
THEY WILL HAVE A GOOD
CONVERSATION AFTER THE GAME.
DAVID: IT‘S BEEN BOTH WAYS.
KARL: BALL FOUR, GLEYBER TORRES.
NOW ROBERTSON IS GOING TO GET
MCKINNEY.
MCKINNEY, TREVINO, AND FULL PAY
HAS BEEN OUTSTANDING IN THE
BOTTOM OF THE ORDER TONIGHT.
4-9, A RUN, THREE DOUBLES.
THE REST OF THE TEAM JUST 2-21.
EDUARDO: YOU HAVE TO BE AWARE OF
THE FIRST PITCH.
MCKINNEY LIKES TO GO AFTER IT.
KARL: 93 MILE AN HOUR CUTTER
DOWN THE MIDDLE.
ESCOBAR ABOUT EVEN WITH THE BAG,
MCNEIL DEEP AT SECOND BASE AND
HOPING FOR A GROUND BALL DOUBLE
MCKINNEY, SLOW ROLLER, AND HE
WILL GET ONE.
STEPPED ON THE BAG IS VIENTO, SO
SECOND AND THIRD NOW.
JOSE TREVINO HAD A BAT, JOSE
TREVINO IS GOING BACK TO THE
BENCH.
LOOKS LIKE BILLY CALHOUN IS
GOING TO PINCH-HIT.
EDUARDO: EMPTYING OUT THE BENCH
THIS INNING.
KARL: A LOT OF GUYS HAVE
CONTRIBUTED TONIGHT FOR THE NEW
YORK YANKEES.
BIG HITS.
AT THE BEGINNING OF THE YEAR YOU
PROBABLY DIDN‘T EXPECT TO BE
MAKING HUGE CONTRIBUTIONS.
CALHOUN IS ANOTHER ONE OF THOSE
GUYS.
A SPOT HERE, SECOND AND THIRD.
FIRST PITCH HIS WAY INSIDE.
EDUARDO: THE ENTIRE BENCH OF
AARON BOONE WILL BE USED THIS
INNING.
HIGASHIOKA ONE WAY OR ANOTHER
WILL COME INTO THIS GAME ON THE
DEFENSIVE STANDPOINT IN THE
BOTTOM HALF OF THE INNING.
KARL: NEXT ONE TO CALHOUN, GETS
A PIECE OF THE CORNER ACCORDING
TO MILLER.
.240 BATTING AVERAGE FOR
CALHOUN, FIVE HOMERS, 16 RUNS
BATTED IN, OPS AT 1725.
ONE BALL, ONE STRIKE.
CALHOUN, CHOPPER.
ESCOBAR CUTS IT OFF, THROWS
ACROSS THE DIAMOND, AND GETS
HIM.
YANKEES THREATENED IN THE TOP OF
THE NINTH, COULD NOT SCORE.
NOW UP TO BRETT BATY, TOMMY
PHAM, AND EDUARDO ESCOBAR.
ROBERTSON PITCHES IN AND OUT OF
TROUBLE.
KARL: A GOOD ONE LAST SUNDAY, WE
HOPE TO HAVE ANOTHER ONE THIS
SUNDAY.
YANKEES-RED SOX.
THIS TIME AT FENWAY PARK.
AVAILABLE ON ESPN DAY FOUR DAYS
AND ESPN RADIO.
WE WILL START AT 6:00 EASTERN
WITH BASEBALL TONIGHT SUNDAY
NIGHT COUNTDOWN.
ALBERT ABREU ON FOR THE YANKEES.
WITH EDUARDO PEREZ, DAVID CONE,
I‘M KARL RAVECH.
FIRST PITCH, BOTTOM OF THE NINTH
INNING WITH A TIE GAME IS IN FOR
A STRIKE TO BRETT BATY.
HE HAS LEFT THE YARD FOUR TIMES
THIS SEASON.
TOMMY PHAM DUE UP NEXT, HE HAS A
DOUBLE AND A SINGLE.
BIG SWING FROM BATY, TERRIFIC
NUMBERS AT THE MINOR LEAGUE
LEVEL.
MOST METS FANS CLAMORING TO GET
INTO THE LINEUP AND REGULARLY
PLAYING.
2-2 FROM ABREU, 98 MILE AN HOUR
SINKER.
DAVID: A BIG ARM, THAT HAS NEVER
BEEN THE QUESTION.
HIS BASE ON BALLS RATE A LITTLE
BIT HIGH.
THAT HAS ALWAYS BEEN THE
QUESTION.
KARL: THIS BALL TO RIGHT.
BOWERS DRIFTING INTO THE CORNER
AND JUST SHORT.
HE IS THERE TO MAKE THE PLAY.
BOWERS IN RIGHT STILL, MCKINNEY
MOVED TO CENTER, CABRERA NOW IN
LEFT FIELD, GLEYBER TORRES AT
SECOND BASE, HIGASHIOKA BEHIND
THE PLATE.
ONE DOWN, DANGEROUS HITTER,
TOMMY PHAM.
A COUPLE OF BASEBALLS APPEARED
TO BE ON THE OUTFIELD WARNING
TRACK.
CABRERA CLEANS UP THE FIELD AND
NOW IT IS PHAM.
FIRST PITCH IS WAY AWAY.
WE ARE TIED AFTER NINE.
MANFRED MANN WILL BE ON SECOND
BASE, AS TONY LIKES TO SAY.
SPECIAL RUNNER.
1-0.
IN AND OUT OF THE GLOVE OF
HIGASHIOKA.
THE METS HAVE NINE WALKOFF WINS
AGAINST THE YANKEES.
DAVID: NOT GIVING IN TO TOMMY
PHAM.
2-0 SLIDER.
EDUARDO: IF YOU THROW IT 2-0,
YOU MIGHT AS WELL THROW IT 3-1.
DAVID: AGREED.
KARL: EIGHT HIM UP ON THE GROUND
TO SHORT.
SINKER AT 98.6.
DAVID: WELL, IF YOU ARE GOING TO
THROW IT LIKE THAT, OK THEN.
99 MILES AN HOUR WITH THAT KIND
OF MOVEMENT.
LOOK AT THAT BALL POURING IN
FROM TOMMY PHAM.
EDUARDO: 3-1 COUNT SWING RIGHT
THERE, A LOT OF LIFE.
KARL: EDUARDO ESCOBAR SWINGS AT
THE FIRST ONE.
IN 2023, THE METS HAVE TWO
WALKOFF WINS, THE YANKEES HAVE
THREE WALKOFF LOSSES.
FOLLOWS NOT OFF, 98 MILE AN HOUR
PITCH FROM ABREU.
DAVID: SORT OF A GREAT EXAMPLE
OF A MODERN-DAY BULLPEN, THE SIX
BEST RELIEVERS THROWING 98, 99
WITH THAT KIND OF MOVEMENT.
2023, TOUGHER TO HIT THAN EVER.
KARL: LAST NIGHT THE YANKEE
BULLPEN, 4.1, AND DID NOT GIVE
UP ANYTHING.
TONIGHT CORDERO GOT TOUCHED UP
FOR A COUPLE OF EARNED RUNS.
1-2.
AFTER CORDERO IS MARINACCIO,
KAHNLE, ABREU.
BRIGHAM GAVE UP TWO EARNED RUNS
AND SINCE THEN, RALEY, DAVAO,
AND ROBERTSON HAVE BEEN LOCKED
DOWN.
OUTSIDE 2-2.
EDUARDO: THE SLIDER HAS BEEN THE
PITCH HE HAS BEEN ABLE TO
CONTROL IN THE ZONE.
KARL: THERE IS MIKE BREEN.
WE SAW THE NBA FINALS, BIG NEW
YORK METS FAN.
SEE IF ESCOBAR CAN END THIS BAD
BOY.
HE IS CONFUSED BY WHAT THE GUY
IN FRONT OF HIM IS DOING.
HE IS LIKE, DOWN IN FRONT.
KARL: YOU SEE COURTSIDE NBA
GAMES.
ESCOBAR IS GONE, 99.
THE YANKEE BULLPEN, AS GOOD AS
IT HAS BEEN ALL YEAR, DELIVERS
HERE LATE.
ARE NACCHIO, KAHNLE, ABREU.
KARL: GERRIT COLE AND JUSTIN
\⁠hKARL: GERRIT COLE AND JUSTIN
VERLANDER COMBINED 12 INNINGS,
SEVEN HITS, ONE EARNED RUN EACH.
COLE HAD EIGHT, VERLANDER SIX.
THE BIG STEEL OF HOME BY ISIAH
KINER-FALEFA AND THE BASERUNNING
MISTAKE BY BRANDON NIMMO.
THE METS WOULD HAVE HAD
BASES-LOADED AND A CHANCE TO
GRAB THE LEAD.
NOW WE GO TO THE 10TH INNING.
HIGASHIOKA IS THE RUNNER AT
SECOND BASE.
VOLPE GOES THE OTHER WAY BUT
THAT ONE IS GOING TO GET OUT OF
PLAY.
DOMINIC LEONE, THE SIXTH MET
PITCHER OF THE NIGHT.
GOOD PITCH THERE.
THAT SEEMS TO BE A SPOT VOLPE IS
VULNERABLE TO.
EDUARDO: HE IS BEARING DOWN WITH
TWO STRIKES TONIGHT, DRIVING IN
THE BOTTOM OF RIGHT FIELD.
WOULD NOT EXPECT ANY OTHER THING
FROM HIM RIGHT NOW.
A LOT MORE CONFIDENCE SINCE
YESTERDAY.
KARL: GOT HIM THERE AND ELEVATED
A LITTLE.
92, WAY OFF THE PLATE.
VOLPE CANNOT ADVANCE HIGASHIOKA.
DAVID: A COUPLE OF DIFFERENT
LOOKS ON LEONE‘S BREAKING
BALL.
KARL: HERE IS BAUERS.
SWING AND A MISS.
GOOD FIGHT THEY ARE TOO.
LEONE ABOUT TWO RUNS OVER HIS
LAST SEVEN GAMES.
OPPOSING BATTERS HITTING .130.
EDUARDO: HIGASHIOKA NOT WITH A
BIG LEAD, BUT DECENT SECONDARY
AT SECOND.
C1
\⁠hC1
TRY TO CATCH IT TO BLOCK IT.
KARL: 97 MILES AN HOUR,
STRAIGHT.
ONE BALL, TWO STRIKES.
SPOILS IT.
DAVID: BAUERS HAS BEEN A TOUGH
OUT FOR ALL METS PITCHERS
TONIGHT.
KARL: ONLY 10 GAMES ON THE
SCHEDULE TOMORROW.
BOTH TEAMS WILL HAVE AN OFF DAY.
BAUERS.
MEMO.
HIGASHIOKA GOES BACK AND HE WILL
STAY PUT.
TWO MEN DOWN AND GIANCARLO
STANTON COMES UP WITH FIRST BASE
OPEN.
ALVAREZ WILL GO OUT AND TALK TO
LEONE.
ALVAREZ IS ON DECK.
LINDOR COMES IN.
HE HAS BEEN A GIANT MET KILLER.
MOST HOME RUNS AGAINST THE METS,
38, AHEAD OF HARPER AND FREEMAN.
MANY OF THOSE ACCUMULATED WHEN
HE WAS WITH THE MARLINS.
24 LONG BALLS AT THIS BALLPARK.
YOU GOING TO PITCH TO HIM?
DAVID: I WONDER WHAT BUCK IS
THINKING.
DO YOU MESS AROUND AND DON‘T
GIVE IN BECAUSE YOU HAVE THIRD
BASE OPEN, OR YOU GO AHEAD AND
PUT UP FOUR?
TRY TO GET STANTON TO CHASE.
DAVID: VERY GOOD LOW-BALL
HITTER.
KARL: MISSES AWAY.
WITH ALL DUE RESPECT TO
DONALDSON, I‘M NOT SURE I AM
FOLLOWING THIS LINE OF THINKING.
YOU ARE GOING TO HAVE YOUR
RUNNER ON AT SECOND.
DAVID: I UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU ARE
SAYING BUT GIANCARLO STANTON
CAME INTO THE SERIES STRUGGLING
AS WELL.
2-0, PUT THEM ON.
KARL: SEE IF HE WOULD CHASE, HE
DIDN‘T ON THE FIRST ONE.
SECOND RUN WAS NOT REALLY
TRACEABLE, NOW DONALDSON WILL
COME UP WITH TWO MEN ON.
IF YOU ARE A MANAGER, YOU HAVE
TO HAVE A LOT OF TRUST IN YOUR
PITCHER.
DAVID: SOMETIMES IT‘S BETTER TO
LET HIM GO TO FIRST BASE.
HERE YOU HAVE DONALDSON.
KARL: HIGASHIOKA, 66.
DONALDSON.
LINDOR BACKS UP, GOES TO SECOND.
THEY WILL NOT SCORE, TOP OF THE
10TH.
RAMIREZ WARMING AND THE YANKEE
BULLPEN.
9-1-2 AS THE METS COME UP IN THE
BOTTOM OF THE
KARL: DONALDSON SENT ONE INTO
THE HOLE.
NOW THE METS HAVE THEIR CHANCE.
ESCOBAR IS THE RUNNER AT SECOND.
RIZZO IS WAY IN.
MARK VIENTOS.
EDUARDO: VIENTOS IS A MIDDLE OF
THE ORDER BAT IN THE MINOR
LEAGUES.
REALLY WOULD BE SURPRISED BUCK
SHOWALTER WOULD PUT HIM HERE.
KARL: RIZZO BACKS UP A BIT BACK
GOT A PIECE OF THE CORNER AT 98.
EDUARDO: MANY AT HOME WOULD SAY
HE IS NOT A BAT GUY NOW.
IT IS HARD WHEN YOU DON‘T HAVE A
PLAYER CONDITIONED AND TRAINED
HOW TO BUNT THE BALL, ESPECIALLY
TOWARDS THIRD WHEN YOU HAVE AN
EXCELLENT THIRD BASEMAN.
DAVID: HE DOESN‘T KNOW HOW TO
BUNT.
KARL: 0-2.
A STARING CONTEST BETWEEN ABREU
AND ESCOBAR.
MISSES IN SIDE.
EDUARDO: OUTFIELD VERY SHALLOW.
KARL: YOU CAN HEAR BILL MILLER,
WHICH IS GREAT.
I HAVE HEARD OTHER PEOPLE
INCLUDING YUSEI THEY HAVE MIK
CS, LET‘S HEAR IT.
IT‘S ALL PART OF THE MINUTIA OF
BASEBALL IN 2023.
NOW VIENTOS IS LOCKED IN, ABREU
CAN GO.
1-2.
WILD SWING, PITCH DOWN AND AWAY
AND HE IS GONE.
HERE COMES BUNIM.
HE HAS RAMIREZ THE LEFTY WARMING
FOR THE LEFTY NIMMO.
DAVID: AFTER ALL THAT, SLIDER
DOWN AND AWAY AND A CHASE.
KARL: THE CHALLENGE OF THE
YANKEES IS GOING TO BE WHEN THEY
GET A LEAD, THEY HAVE A BULLPENS
THAT HAS SO MANY WEAPONS.
WE WILL TAKE A TIMEOUT
KARL: AN OPPORTUNITY FOR BRANDON
NIMMO TO  EXORCISE A COUPLE OF
DEMONS.
LAST NIGHT THE FLY BALL HAD A
CHANCE AND HE WAS FRUSTRATED
WITH HIMSELF.
YANKEES WON 7-6.
TONIGHT MARTE DELIVERED THE
TYING RUN AND NIMMO DID NOT LOOK
AHEAD OF HIM.
HE GOT THROWN OUT GOING BACK TO
SECOND BASE.
HAD HE NOT, THEY WOULD HAVE HAD
THE BASES LOADED AND ANOTHER
CHANCE TO SCORE.
WITH THE SYMMETRY OF BASEBALL,
NIMMO HAS A CHANCE AGAINST
RAMIREZ, WHO HAS BEEN DYNAMITE.
LEFTY ON LEFT.
ESCOBAR REPRESENTS THE WINNING
RUN.
THE FIRST BENCH IN FOR A STRIKE.
EDUARDO: CONTINUES TO PLAY VERY
SHALLOW.
KARL: NIMMO, RIGHT FIELD DEEP.
STILL GOING BACK.
IT‘S OFF THE WALL.
ESCOBAR, A SLOW START AT SECOND
BASE.
HE IS BEING WAVED IN.
HERE HE COMES.
AND THE METS WALK IT OFF.
WHAT A RELIEF FOR BRANDON NIMMO.
EDUARDO ESCOBAR WAS TWO FEET OFF
SECOND BASE WHEN THAT BALL HIT
THE WALL AS HE WAS ALLOWING
BAUERS TO GO BACK.
BRANDON NIMMO DELIVERING THE BIG
HIT.
DAVID: WITH ONE OUT, NO REASON
TO BE ANYWHERE NEAR THAT BAG.
NONETHELESS, NIMMO‘S BIG HIT IS
A GREAT DEODORANT FOR AN UGLY
GAME.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN A BRUTAL LOSS
HAD THEY NOT COME THROUGH.
EDUARDO: BAUERS HAD TO GO A LONG
WAY TO GET THAT BASEBALL.
MOST LIKELY HE MAKES THIS PLAY
AND THEN YOU HAVE A TAG UP WITH
THE RUNNER AT SECOND.
THINGS CHANGE FOR THE NEW YORK
METS.
THERE IS NO REASON FOR HIM TO BE
TAGGING THE ONE OUT.
DAVID: AWFUL BASERUNNING THAT HE
GETS AWAY WITH.
KARL: HE DOES.
BAUERS AT THE WALL.
THE THROW FROM TORRES DID NOT
HAVE A BUNCH OF MUSTARD ON IT
EITHER BECAUSE HE PROBABLY
THOUGHT ESCOBAR HAD HIT HOME
BASE.
THE METS AND UP SPLITTING THE
SUBWAY SERIES TWO GAMES THAT.
DAVID: A VERY UGLY NIGHT TURNS
INTO A HUGE WIN FOR THE METS.
KARL: WHITE SOX LEAD THE DODGERS
2.
WE WILL SEND YOU THERE RIGHT
NOW.
WE WILL SEE YOU SUNDAY NIGHT,
RED SOX AND YANKEES.
BRANDON NIMMO, THAT‘S THE BEAUTY
OF BASEBALL.
THE SUN USUALLY COMES UP BUT WE
HAVE NOT SEEN THE SUN COME UP
AFTER THAT BLUNDER.
OUR ENTIRE CREW BACK IN BRISTOL
LED BY ANDY JACOBSON, I AM KARL
RAVECH.
WE SEND YOU OUT WEST NOW TO THE
DODGERS AND WHITE SOX.